[Bae Seongjae] This is the Minnesota Wild uniform. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] このミネソタ・ワイルドのユニフォームです。です。さあ。
[Staff] Okay
[Staff] さあ
[Bae Seongjae]  I'll record the opening comments.
[Bae Seongjae] オープニングメント録音します。
[Bae Seongjae] Perfect
[Bae Seongjae] 完璧な
[Bae Seongjae] Hello everyone, welcome to Bae Seongjae's TEN on Sunday, March 1st, 2026
[Bae Seongjae] こんにちは。2026年3月1日日曜日、Bae SeongjaeのTENにいらっしゃった皆さん
[Bae Seongjae] Welcome. I'm Bae Seongjae. Our first song was Hearts2Hearts' STYLE
[Bae Seongjae] いらっしゃいませ。Bae Seongjaeです。最初の曲はHearts2HeartsのSTYLEを
[Bae Seongjae] Today's headline was Hearts2Hearts finding their perfect
[Bae Seongjae] お届けしました。今日のヘッドラインは、Hearts2Hearts1周年に見つけた完璧な
[Bae Seongjae] color on their 1st anniversary. Uh, in 2025 alone, there were about
[Bae Seongjae] カラーでした。えー、昨年2025年にK-POPアイドルでデビューしたチームだけで
[Bae Seongjae] 70-80 teams that debuted as K-pop idols. Among them, surviving and having their own team color
[Bae Seongjae] 70、80チームになるんですよ。その中で生き残って自分たちのチームカラーを持って
[Bae Seongjae] and making their songs known to the public isn't easy. After debuting and sweeping nine rookie awards
[Bae Seongjae] 大衆に歌を知らせることは簡単なことじゃないですよね。デビューして1年間、新人賞
[Bae Seongjae] in one year, girl group Hearts2Hearts with their members' balanced charm and addictive house dance tracks that
[Bae Seongjae] 9つを総なめしたガールグループHearts2Heartsは、メンバーたちのバランスの取れた魅力と、一度聞けば
[Bae Seongjae] keep spinning in your head once you hear them, consistently pushed forward with razor-sharp
[Bae Seongjae] ずっと頭に回る中毒性の強いハウス・ダンス曲を継続的に押し出しながら、キレキレの
[Bae Seongjae] performances to gradually make their name known, and now a year after debut,
[Bae Seongjae] パフォーマンスで披露して名前を少しずつ知らせて、デビュー1周年が過ぎた今は
[Bae Seongjae] they're finding their color and their new songs are getting great reactions. And
[Bae Seongjae] 自分たちのカラーを見つけながら新曲も反応がとても良いです。そして
[Bae Seongjae] Hearts2Hearts' original content is also getting good reactions. These bubbly members have great
[Bae Seongjae] Hearts2Heartsは自主コンテンツも反応が良いんですが、この愛らしいメンバーたちの仲も
[Bae Seongjae] chemistry and their honest daily life moments are getting really good reactions. Today these ladies are coming
[Bae Seongjae] 良くて正直な日常の姿も反応がとても良いです。今日この方々がPae Seongjae's TENに
[Bae Seongjae] to Bae TEN. Everyone, welcome them with uncle smiles and let's have a fun time
[Bae Seongjae] いらっしゃいます。皆さん、おじさんの微笑みで迎えながら楽しい時間を過ごして
[Bae Seongjae] together. Now, today is the day for the girl group guest corner you're always waiting for and looking forward to,
[Bae Seongjae] いただければと思います。さあ、今日は皆さんがいつも待っていて期待しているガールグループ招待席コーナー
[Bae Seongjae] Produce 1077, and SM's youngest girl group Hearts2Hearts'
[Bae Seongjae] Produce 1077をやる日で、SM Entertainmentの末っ子ガールグループHearts2Heartsの
[Bae Seongjae] Yuha and Stella are here as representatives. Please wait a moment for our meeting with the '07-liners Nutella duo,
[Bae Seongjae] Yuhaさん、Stellaさんのお二人が代表で出演されます。'07-liners Nutella duoのお二人との
[Bae Seongjae] and for Bae Seongjae's TEN, if you come to our YouTube
[Bae Seongjae] 出会い、少しお待ちください。Bae Seongjae's TENは録音時間に合わせてYouTubeの
[Bae Seongjae] channel or Chzzk during recording time, you can watch the full
[Bae Seongjae] ライブチャンネル、緑の窓、Chzzkにいらっしゃれば編集される前の録音全過程
[Bae Seongjae] unedited recording process. Especially for Produce 1077, there are many edited parts,
[Bae Seongjae] フル映像をすべて見ることができます。特にProduce 1077は編集される部分が
[Bae Seongjae] so make sure to check out
[Bae Seongjae] 多いので必ずフルバージョンを
[Bae Seongjae] the full version. We'll be back after the commercial.
[Bae Seongjae] ご覧ください。CM聞いて戻ります。
[Bae Seongjae] Is it on?
[Bae Seongjae] ついてる？
[Staff] Yes.
[Staff] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, I want to eat a Nutella sandwich.
[Bae Seongjae] わあ、Nutellaサンドイッチ食べたいな。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, okay, here
[Bae Seongjae] あ、さあ、ここ
[Bae Seongjae] it's marked.
[Bae Seongjae] マーキングされました。
[Bae Seongjae] 97 97, same age, right?
[Bae Seongjae] 97、97、合番ですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Welcome, welcome, welcome. Oh my, thank you.
[Bae Seongjae] いらっしゃいませ。いらっしゃいませ。いらっしゃいませ。です。あらまあ、ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Welcome.
[Bae Seongjae] いらっしゃいませ。
[Bae Seongjae] Thank you for coming and rushing over like this.
[Bae Seongjae] お疲れさまで、こうしてまたすぐ駆けつけてくださってありがとうございます。
[Stella] Oh, there it is.
[Stella] あ、ここにあるんだ。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes, yes, yes. It's on here so all the sound goes in too.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。はい。はい。ここついてるので音も全部入りますよ。
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Everyone's saying they can't believe it.
[Bae Seongjae] やあ、信じられないって皆さん言ってますね。
[Stella] It's an honor. We're honored. Please take care of us.
[Stella] 光栄です。私たちが光栄です。よろしくお願いします。
[Bae Seongjae] Please take care of us. Please take care of us.
[Bae Seongjae] よろしくお願いします。よろしくお願いします。
[Bae Seongjae] Those born in '07 are now
[Bae Seongjae] 07年生は今
[Stella] This year.
[Stella] 今年。
[Stella] We became adults. Congratulations.
[Stella] ようやく成人になったんですよ。おめでとうございます。
[Stella] Thank you.
[Stella] ありがとうございます。
[Stella] Wow. Wow. Amazing.
[Stella] うわあ。うわあ。やばい。
[Bae Seongjae] There are a lot of uncle fans here too.
[Bae Seongjae] このまたおじさんファンの方々がすごく多いんですよ。
[Stella] Ah, hello uncles.
[Stella] あ、おじさんたちこんにちは。
[Bae Seongjae] Uncles, older uncles, and grandfathers are here too.
[Bae Seongjae] おじさんたち、お兄さんたち、あとおじいさんたちもいらっしゃいます。ここ
[Stella] Ah, grandfather
[Stella] あ、おじいさん
[Bae Seongjae] Yes, grandfather,
[Bae Seongjae] おじいさんはい、
[Staff] indeed.
[Staff] います。
[Bae Seongjae] Is your manager treating you well?
[Bae Seongjae] マネージャーさんは優しくしてくれますか？
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Stella] Yes. He treats us so well.
[Stella] はい。とても優しくしてくれます。
[Stella] Have you eaten?
[Stella] お食事はされましたか？
[Bae Seongjae] Dinner, ah, you haven't eaten, right? Oh my, it's late
[Bae Seongjae] 夕食、あ、食べてないですよね？あらまぁ遅くに
[Bae Seongjae] What did you eat?
[Bae Seongjae] 何を食べましたか？
[Stella] Uh, chicken and pizza
[Stella] えーとチキンピザ
[Bae Seongjae] Chicken... for someone who's actively promoting, you ate really well. Yeah
[Bae Seongjae] チキン活動中の割にはとてもよく食べましたね。はい
[Stella] I love eating
[Stella] 私食べることが好きで
[Yuha] Mm
[Yuha] うん
[Staff] Chicken
[Staff] チキン
[Yuha] Ah, since we're together, are you from SM?
[Yuha] あ一緒にいるからSM Entertainmentの方ですか？
[Bae Seongjae] Me?
[Bae Seongjae] 私ですか？
[Bae Seongjae] It's SM C&C, so yes, we could say we're from the same group. Oh amazing.
[Bae Seongjae] SM CNCですから、はい同じ系列だと言えますね。あすごい。
[Bae Seongjae] As a fellow SM... senior... when did you join SM?
[Bae Seongjae] 一応SM先輩、いつからSM Entertainmentに入られましたか？
[Yuha] 2017.
[Yuha] 2017年。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, you're a great senior then.
[Bae Seongjae] あ大先輩でいらっしゃいますね。
[Bae Seongjae] I'm 2024. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] 私2024年。はい。
[Stella] Ah
[Stella] あ
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, you're 7 years my senior.
[Bae Seongjae] え7年も後輩ですね。
[Stella] I'm 2023
[Stella] 私は23年
[Bae Seongjae] You're almost 2 years my senior.
[Bae Seongjae] 2年近い先輩でいらっしゃいますね。
[Bae Seongjae] 2017?
[Bae Seongjae] 17年ですか？
[Yuha] Yes. When I was young.
[Yuha] はい。小さい時に。
[Bae Seongjae] So when you were 10?
[Bae Seongjae] じゃあ10歳の時？
[Yuha] 11 years old.
[Yuha] 11歳。
[Bae Seongjae] At 11 years old. Oh my.
[Bae Seongjae] 11歳の時。あらまぁ。
[Bae Seongjae] Please take care of us, senior.
[Bae Seongjae] よろしくお願いします先輩
[Bae Seongjae] How many hours of sleep do you get these days?
[Bae Seongjae] 最近何時間お休みになりますか？
[Yuha] Now that promotions started, I can't sleep.
[Yuha] もう活動始まったから寝れません
[Stella] We can't sleep much now.
[Stella] もうあまり寝れません。
[Bae Seongjae] Can't sleep, right? Sleep in the car.
[Bae Seongjae] 寝れないってことですね。車で寝て。
[Stella] Yes. That's right. During waiting time.
[Stella] はい。そうです。待機時間に。
[Stella] Mm.
[Stella] うん。
[Staff] Ah, let's test this once.
[Staff] あ、ちょっとテストしてみます。
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Please give us a greeting.
[Bae Seongjae] 挨拶を一度お願いします。
[Staff] Yes.
[Staff] はい。
[Staff] Uh,
[Staff] え、
[Staff] Shall we start with Stella? [Stella] Hello. I'm Stella from Hearts2Hearts.
[Staff] ステラさんからやりましょうか？ [Stella] こんにちは。Hearts2Heartsのステラです。
[Stella] I'm so happy to be here today.
[Stella] 今日出演できてとても嬉しいです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh my, your voice is so nice.
[Bae Seongjae] あらまぁ声がとても良いですね。
[Yuha] Thank you.
[Yuha] ありがとうございます。
[Yuha] Hello. I'm Yuha from Hearts2Hearts. Please take care of us.
[Yuha] こんにちは。ユハです。よろしくお願いします。
[Staff] Oh, thank you.
[Staff] いや〜、ありがとうございます。
[Staff] When you speak, since the MC is here, we do it like this but
[Staff] お話しする時、どうしてもMCがここにいるので、こうしてるんですが
[Staff] the microphone needs to be close to your mouth for good audio. So always
[Staff] マイクを口の近くに持ってないとよく入らないんですよ。なので常に
[Staff] when you speak into the microphone, keep it close.
[Staff] マイクで発言する時は近くでお願いします。
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Speaker] Got it.
[Speaker] わかりました。
[Bae Seongjae] Bae Seongjae will keep going until we meet 1,077 amazing female stars.
[Bae Seongjae] ペ・ソンジェが人気の女性スターを1077人に出会うまでずっと一緒にします。
[Bae Seongjae] Produce 1077.
[Bae Seongjae] プロデュース1077。
[Bae Seongjae]  Today's guests, Rookie Award 9-time winners since debut
[Bae Seongjae] 今日のゲストは新人賞9冠王
[Bae Seongjae] Their 1st anniversary, new song RUDE comeback, double celebration making every day happy. Bold and
[Bae Seongjae] デビュー1周年、新曲RUDEカムバックまで重なる慶事で毎日がハッピーな方たちですよね。生意気で
[Bae Seongjae] cute and lively Gen Z girl group Hearts2Hearts' Nutella duo, Yuha and Stella,
[Bae Seongjae] 可愛くて明るいGen-Z ガールグループ、Hearts2HeartsのNutellaコンビ、ユハさん、ステラ
[Bae Seongjae] welcome!
[Bae Seongjae] さん、お二人、いらっしゃいませ。
[Stella] Hello.
[Stella] こんにちは。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, nice to meet you. Yes
[Bae Seongjae] あ、お会いできて嬉しいです。はい
[Bae Seongjae] How about introducing yourselves one by one? [Stella] Yes. Yes. Hello. I'm Stella from Hearts2Hearts.
[Bae Seongjae] お一人ずつご挨拶をお願いできますか？[Stella] はい。はい。こんにちは。Hearts2Heartsのステラです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh my, thank you. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] いやいや、ありがとうございます。はい。
[Yuha] Hello. I'm Yuha from Hearts2Hearts.
[Yuha] こんにちは。Hearts2Heartsのユハです。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes, nice to meet you.
[Bae Seongjae] はい、お会いできて嬉しいです。
[Bae Seongjae] So, we do this broadcast with the chat window open. Bae TEN. Yes,
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、私たちこうやってチャット画面を開けて放送してるんですよ。ペテン。はい、
[Bae Seongjae] so since it's live, you don't need to be nervous. These people are all nice. Yes. They just can't
[Bae Seongjae] なので生放送だから緊張する必要ないですよ。この方たちみんないい人たちで。はい。今、悪口は言え
[Bae Seongjae] talk back. That's right.
[Bae Seongjae] ないんですよ。そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] These people are very RUDE. Yes. They're RUDE uncles but yes, still
[Bae Seongjae] います。この人たちすごくルードな人たちなんですよ。はい。ルードなおじさんたちなんですが、はい、それでも
[Bae Seongjae] they'll be very warm to you. Yes yes
[Bae Seongjae] あなたたちにはとても優しいと思います。はいはい
[Bae Seongjae] So Yuha and Stella together, we saw the Nutella combo. Uh, how do
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、ユハ、ステラ合わせてNutellaコンビで拝見しました。あ、この方たち
[Bae Seongjae] you find the chat? What's your first impression?
[Bae Seongjae] そのチャットの第一印象はいかがですか？
[Yuha] Uh, really
[Yuha] え、本当に
[Bae Seongjae] RUDE, right? Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] ルードでしょう？はい。
[Bae Seongjae] They're very RUDE people. Yes. And shy. Yes. They're RUDE to me
[Bae Seongjae] とてもルードな人たちなんですよ。はい。恥ずかしがり屋な人たちで。はい。私に
[Bae Seongjae] so don't be too
[Bae Seongjae] ルードなことだから、あまり
[Bae Seongjae] flustered, please
[Bae Seongjae] 慌てないでお願いし
[Bae Seongjae] They're only RUDE to me.
[Bae Seongjae] 私にだけルードな人たちです。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, you started music shows this week and you're doing another music show today and
[Bae Seongjae] え、今週から音楽番組始められましたが、今日も音楽番組を今
[Bae Seongjae] coming here, so you look so bright. Yes. You were also an MC, right?
[Bae Seongjae] してきて、あ、とても華やかで、はい。MCもしてきましたし、そうですよね？
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Oh my, congratulations.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。いやいや、おめでとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Are the other members resting now? Or do they have other schedules? [Stella] They went home.
[Bae Seongjae] 他のメンバーは今休んでますか？それとも別のスケジュールがありますか？ [Stella] 退勤しました。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, but only you two worked hard to come here. Thank you.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、でもお二人だけこうやって頑張って来てくださったんですね。ありがとうございます。
[Stella] Not at all.
[Stella] いえいえ。
[Bae Seongjae] So let's go to the promotional time. Uh, we'll play Hearts2Hearts' new song RUDE as background music.
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、それでは、大々的な宣伝タイム行ってみましょう。え、Hearts2Heartsの新曲RUDEを背景音楽として流しますので
[Bae Seongjae] While the song plays, please do the team introduction and song promotion that every team does.
[Bae Seongjae] 曲が流れる間、必ずするチーム紹介、曲の宣伝をしてください。
[Bae Seongjae] Let's start right away.
[Bae Seongjae] すぐに始めます。
[Staff] Going in.
[Staff] 入っていきます。
[Bae Seongjae] So Hearts2Hearts, since this is our first meeting, could you introduce your team name? Yes. We
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、Hearts2Hearts、初対面なのでチーム名の紹介をしていただけますか？はい。私たち
[Stella] Hearts2Hearts means heart to heart, and we want to convey our hearts through our music and performances
[Stella] Hearts2Heartsは心から心へという意味で、私たちが音楽とパフォーマンスで私たちの心を
[Stella] through our music and performances.
[Stella] 伝えたいという意味を持っています。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, what a beautiful name. Hearts. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、名前がとても素敵ですね。ハートです。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] And this is SM's first 8-member girl group in 4 years and 3 months since aespa.
[Bae Seongjae] えっと、SM Entertainmentがaespa以来4年3ヶ月ぶりに出した8人組ガールズグループなんですよね。
[Staff] Yes.
[Staff] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] S2U, are there any advantages to having many members?
[Bae Seongjae] S2Uの皆さん、メンバーが多いことの長所は何かありますか？
[Yuha] Uh, when ordering delivery food, the menu variety is diverse.
[Yuha] えっと、デリバリーを注文する時にメニューが多様だ。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, so you can order different things and everyone can eat.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、全部違うものを頼んで食べられるから。
[Yuha] We can eat eight different things.
[Yuha] 8種類食べられる。
[Bae Seongjae] One bite each. Uh, are there any members who are sensitive about having their food taken?
[Bae Seongjae] 一口ずつ。えっと、食べ物取られるのに敏感な方はいませんか？
[Yuha] We don't have that, I think we're okay.
[Yuha] 私たちはいないので大丈夫だと思います。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh really? Uh, so you order enough. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そうですか？えっと、でも十分な量を注文するんですね。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Are there any disadvantages to having many members?
[Bae Seongjae] メンバーが多くて短所はありませんか？
[Stella] The waiting time is long. That's right.
[Stella] 待機時間が長い。そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Waiting time.
[Bae Seongjae] 待機時間。
[Stella] Yes. And prep time is long too.
[Stella] はい。準備時間も長いです。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, like going to the salon or using the bathroom and such.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、美容室に行くとか、あとはその、お風呂を使うとか、そういうこと。
[Bae Seongjae] How are you using your dorm right now?
[Bae Seongjae] 今どのように宿舎を使ってますか？
[Yuha] Yes.
[Yuha] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Eight people in one dorm?
[Bae Seongjae] 8人で一つの宿舎。
[Yuha] We split up by a few people [Bae Seongjae] Ah, I see. Uh, on the 20th you released your new single album
[Yuha] 何人かずつに分かれて [Bae Seongjae] あ、そうなんですね。えっと、先月20日に新しいシングルアルバム
[Bae Seongjae] RUDE!. Looking at the song title, there's an exclamation mark.
[Bae Seongjae] RUDE!をリリースしました。曲のタイトル表記を見ると感嘆符が付いてるんですよね。
[Bae Seongjae] How should I say this? RUDE?
[Bae Seongjae] これはどう言えばいいんですか？RUDE!って？
[Stella] Uh, kind of like RU-, like RU-
[Stella] えっと、ちょっとルー、こんな感じでルー！
[Staff] Ah, I did it too harshly, that was tacky. I
[Staff] あ、こんな風に私が強すぎてダサかったですね。私
[Bae Seongjae] That's tacky. Not RUDE like that, but RU-
[Bae Seongjae] これがダサいね。RUDE!じゃなくてルー！
[Bae Seongjae] Yes, everyone should say RU-. Yes. Could you introduce what kind of song it is?
[Bae Seongjae] はい、皆さんルー！ってやってください。はい。どんな曲なのか紹介していただけますか？
[Yuha] Uh, RUDE! is a house genre dance song.
[Yuha] えっと、RUDE!はハウスジャンルのダンス曲で、
[Yuha] Uh, it's a song with very cute rebellion about not being bound by the rules set by the world.
[Yuha] えっと、世の中に決められた規則に縛られないという、とても可愛い反抗を込めた曲です。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, the song is so good. Today, based on our recording, you did your first music show and
[Bae Seongjae] あ、曲がとても良かったです。今日その録音基準で初の音楽番組をやって
[Stella] came running here - how was the stage reaction? S2U cheered for us so
[Stella] 駆けつけてくださいましたが、ステージの反応はどうでしたか？S2Uがとてもとても熱く応援してくださって
[Stella] passionately
[Stella] くれて
[Stella] Yes. Our hearts felt so warm.
[Stella] はい。心がとても温かくなりました。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, this is really a great start.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、これは本当にスタートが良いですね。
[Bae Seongjae] And Yuha, you're the intro fairy with such a pretty voice, for this song RU-
[Bae Seongjae] そしてユハさんは音色がとても綺麗なイントロ妖精なんですが、今回の曲ルー
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, did I cut it too short?
[Bae Seongjae] あ、短すぎましたか？
[Stella] RUDE! Ah, that was good.
[Stella] ルー！あ、良かったですよ。
[Bae Seongjae] DE!. Could you possibly do a little a cappella live of RUDE!'s intro?
[Bae Seongjae] ですね。ルー！のイントロ、もしかして無伴奏ライブちょっと可能ですか？
[Yuha] Yes.
[Yuha] はい。
[Yuha] Should I do it?
[Yuha] やりますか？
[Bae Seongjae] Start. [Yuha] Who said
[Bae Seongjae] スタート。[Yuha] 誰が何と言っても
[Yuha] ordinary things are boring. Everything as I want.
[Yuha] 平凡なのは退屈 すべて思いのままに
[Bae Seongjae] Wow.
[Bae Seongjae] やー！
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, thank you. Yes. Some people said this is what radio is about. Ears
[Bae Seongjae] あー、ありがとうございます。はい。これがラジオだって言ってる方々がいて。耳が
[Bae Seongjae] melting. Voice fairy. As expected of SM. Yes. Someone said their eardrums feel refreshed
[Bae Seongjae] とろける。音生妖精。さすがSM。はい。鼓膜が爽やかになるって言ってる方も
[Bae Seongjae] too.
[Bae Seongjae] いますよ。
[Bae Seongjae] And February 24th was your first debut anniversary. Congratulations.
[Bae Seongjae] そして去る2月24日がデビュー1周年でした。おめでとうございます。
[Stella] Thank you.
[Stella] ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, you had your first fan meeting last weekend for your first anniversary.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、デビュー1周年に合わせて初ファンミーティングを先週末にやったんですよね。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. How was the fan meeting? [Yuha] It was our very first fan meeting
[Bae Seongjae] はい。ファンミーティングはいかがでしたか？ [Yuha] 私たちにとって初めてのファンミーティングだったんですが
[Yuha] and some members cried, and it was our first time in a space with just our S2U fans
[Yuha] すごく泣いてるメンバーもいたし、S2U私たちのファンの方たちとこうやってファンの方だけがいる
[Yuha] so it felt really new.
[Yuha] 空間は初めてだったので、すごく新鮮でしたね。
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah, someone said time really flies, yes,
[Bae Seongjae] おい、時間って本当に早いって言ってる方がいて、はい、
[Bae Seongjae] right.
[Bae Seongjae] その通りですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Suyeon Gongu asked what's the most memorable episode from the past year
[Bae Seongjae] その수연공구さんが活動した去る1年間で最も記憶に残るエピソードは
[Bae Seongjae] of your activities?
[Bae Seongjae] なんですか？って質問されてるんですが。
[Stella] Personally, I think I'll never forget our debut showcase
[Stella] 私は個人的に私たちのデビューショーケースが本当に忘れられない気がするんですが
[Stella] since it was our first time performing on stage and meeting fans for the first time, so I was really
[Stella] やっぱり初めてステージに立ったし、ファンの方に初めてお会いしたので、その時すごく
[Stella] nervous but it was really impressive.
[Stella] 緊張したんですが、それがすごく印象的で嬉しかった気がします。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh. So it was your first time showing yourselves, how did you feel at that moment?
[Bae Seongjae] うん。つまり初めてお披露目するんだから、その時どう、その時心にパッと
[Bae Seongjae] Or did you feel like you wanted to show more but had some regrets?
[Bae Seongjae] 浮かんでましたか？それとも、あ、なんかもっと見せたかったのに、そんな物足りなさがあったのか
[Stella] Since it was our first time, it was a bit disappointing, but I feel proud because I think we did our best.
[Stella] まあ初めてだったので少し物足りなかったですが、なんか全力を尽くした気がして誇らしいです。
[Bae Seongjae] Nice. I see. Now, for your first anniversary, you donated 50 million won under your fan club name
[Bae Seongjae] おお。そうですね。さあ、1周年に合わせて女性青少年支援のためにファンクラブ名
[Bae Seongjae] S2U to support women and youth. Wow, whose
[Bae Seongjae] S2Uで5千万ウォンを寄付しました。わあ、これ本当に誰の
[Bae Seongjae] idea was this?
[Bae Seongjae] アイデアですか？
[Yuha] All of our members discussed it together, since it's our first anniversary, let's do something meaningful
[Yuha] 私たちメンバー全員で一緒に、1周年だから意味のあることをやってみようということで
[Yuha] so we did it.
[Yuha] やりました。
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, such a large amount. Yes, already as rookies
[Bae Seongjae] いやー、高額を。はい、もうルーキーから
[Bae Seongjae] And following the Korean fan meeting, throughout March you have New York North America showcase, Jakarta
[Bae Seongjae] そして韓国ファンミーティングに続いて3月ずっとニューヨーク北米ショーケース、ジャカルタ、ジャカルタ
[Bae Seongjae] fan meeting, right?
[Bae Seongjae] ファンミーティングですよね？
[Yuha] Yes.
[Yuha] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. You're also preparing overseas performances. What are you preparing?
[Bae Seongjae] はい。海外公演も準備中です。どんなことを準備してますか？
[Yuha] Oh, we're preparing to show RUDE and also many cover songs, and we plan
[Yuha] えっと、今回RUDEと、また多くのカバー曲も見せようと準備中で、はい。今回
[Yuha] to show all the setlists we did in Korea. Yes.
[Yuha] 韓国でやったセットリストは全部見せる予定です。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, I see. Yes. You must be really busy right now, can't even sleep properly, right?
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そうですね。はい。それでも今もう寝る暇もなく忙しいですよね？
[Bae Seongjae] But when you go overseas, you might get some sleep on the flight, right? Yes, that's right.
[Bae Seongjae] 海外に行く時は行く道中で少し寝れるかもしれないしね？ はい、そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] In the year since debut, you've won rookie awards
[Bae Seongjae] デビューして1年の間に新人賞をなんと
[Bae Seongjae] nine times. Wow, really
[Bae Seongjae] 9回受賞しました。いやー、本当に
[Bae Seongjae] you became the artist with the most rookie award wins last year. Do you have any acceptance speech
[Bae Seongjae] 昨年デビューしたアーティストの中で最多新人賞受賞者になったんですが、もし受賞の
[Stella] that you haven't done? I think we've done them all, but still
[Stella] 何か言い忘れたことありますか？全部言った気がしますが、それでも
[Stella] We were so so honored, and something we always talked about since before our debut was that we must
[Stella] 本当に本当に光栄で、デビュー前からずっと話してたのが、絶対
[Stella] win the Rookie Award, and we ended up winning nine, so thank you so so much.
[Stella] 新人賞を取ろうって言ってたのに、9個ももらえて本当に本当にありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, rookie award hunter group, a group with great potential
[Bae Seongjae] おい、新人賞ハンターグループ、期待値の高いグループ
[Bae Seongjae] Finally, can one of you do an acrostic poem with your fandom name S2U for promotion?
[Bae Seongjae] 最後に代表で一人、ファンダム名S2Uで宣伝三行詩可能ですか？うん
[Stella] Yuha's good at acrostic poems.
[Stella] ユハが上手です。三行詩を
[Bae Seongjae] Immediately passing it off
[Bae Seongjae] すぐ丸投げするのか
[Bae Seongjae] Let's go, 'S'
[Bae Seongjae] いってみよう、ハ
[Yuha] Hearts2Hearts' RUDE
[Yuha] Hearts2HeartsのRUDE
[Bae Seongjae] 'U'
[Bae Seongjae] ツ
[Yuha] I recommend it.
[Yuha] 推薦します。
[Yuha] Wow, nice
[Yuha] わあ、いいね
[Bae Seongjae] Good.
[Bae Seongjae] いいですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Alright, we've done this blatant promo time. Now it's time for
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、こうやって堂々とプロモーションタイムをやってみましたが、今度はキーワードトークタイムに
[Bae Seongjae] keyword talk time. We're introducing keywords for Hearts2Hearts and Yuha and Stella.
[Bae Seongjae] 行きます。通称ハキソ、Hearts2Hearts、そしてユハ、ステラのキーワードを紹介します。
[Staff] Woo
[Staff] うー
[Bae Seongjae] So the first keyword is SM. Yes. Hearts2Hearts, SM Entertainment's youngest girl group
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、最初のキーワードはSM。はい。SMエンターテインメントの末っ子ガールグループ
[Bae Seongjae] and I'm from the same company too.
[Bae Seongjae] Hearts2Heartsですが、僕も同じ系列会社なんですよ。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, I was trying to sort out the seniority here, but I'm actually
[Bae Seongjae] あー、ちょっとその軍番整理をしてみようと思ったんですが、僕はユハさんよりもなんと
[Bae Seongjae] a whole 7 years junior to Yuha in terms of joining the company. Yes. And to Stella
[Bae Seongjae] 7年も入社後輩でして。はい。ステラ
[Bae Seongjae] about 2 years junior. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] さんよりは2年ほど。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] So it feels like a junior is hosting right now. Yes. Someone said bow your head,
[Bae Seongjae] なので今ちょっと後輩が進行してる感じになってます。はい。頭
[Bae Seongjae] someone said 'good', someone said bow
[Bae Seongjae] 下げろって言った方もいるし、大丈夫って言った方もいるし
[Bae Seongjae] in greeting
[Bae Seongjae] 挨拶しろって言った方もいるし
[Bae Seongjae] Uh Yuha, you got cast by SM three times?
[Bae Seongjae] あー、ユハさんはSMでだけキャスティングを3回も受けたんですか？
[Yuha] Uh that's right.
[Yuha] あー、そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] On the street? Yes
[Bae Seongjae] 街で？はい
[Yuha] All three times on the street
[Yuha] 3回とも街で
[Bae Seongjae] Uh where was it? I heard earlier that you were ten
[Bae Seongjae] あー、どこで、さっき聞いてみると10歳の
[Bae Seongjae] years old, so was it at school or? Yes
[Bae Seongjae] 時って言うと、どうやって、その学校ですか？それともはい
[Yuha] My hometown is Wonju, Gangwon Province
[Yuha] 僕の実家が江原道原州なんですが
[Yuha] I got cast once in front of my elementary school when I was in 4th grade
[Yuha] 小学校4年生の時、学校の前でキャスティングを一度受けて
[Yuha] Then I transferred schools when I came to Seoul for trainee life, and got cast again in front of that middle school
[Yuha] それでソウルに練習生活で転校してきたんですが、その中学校の前でまた
[Yuha] and
[Yuha] キャスティングされて
[Yuha] the last time was when I went to the dentist
[Yuha] 最後は歯医者に行った時にキャスティングを
[Bae Seongjae] I see. At the dentist, in the waiting room together
[Bae Seongjae] されたんですね。歯医者だと一緒に待合室で
[Yuha] In the dentist's elevator
[Yuha] 歯医者のエレベーターで
[Yuha] Amazing
[Yuha] やばい
[Bae Seongjae] Ah in the elevator, like 'oh what a pretty kid' or something
[Bae Seongjae] あー、エレベーターで「あー、なんてかわいい子が」って感じで
[Bae Seongjae] Oh I see. Someone's asking if it's because your teeth are so straight.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そうなんですね。歯並びがきれいだからじゃないかって
[Bae Seongjae] They say SM staff are always out scouting
[Bae Seongjae] SM職員たちがすごく歩き回ってるって言うし
[Bae Seongjae] But managers probably always think like that.
[Bae Seongjae] いや、でもマネージャーさんたちは実際いつもそんな考えをしながらいると思います。
[Bae Seongjae] Like 'oh there's a good person, there's a good kid.' Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] あー、いい人がいるな、いい子がいるなって。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] It wasn't the same manager who cast you, right? [Yuha] Uh, they were all different people I think.
[Bae Seongjae] 同じマネージャーがキャスティングしたんじゃないですよね？[Yuha] あー、みんな違う方だったと思います。
[Bae Seongjae] It's not like they kept persistently coming back after you rejected them, then following you to the dentist
[Bae Seongjae] 三顧の礼式で来たけど断られたから、また次に来て歯医者まで
[Bae Seongjae] but different people each time, yes.
[Bae Seongjae] ついてきたってことじゃなくて、それぞれ違う方たちが、はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Stella
[Bae Seongjae] ステラ
[Bae Seongjae] you
[Bae Seongjae] さんは、はい。
[Bae Seongjae] auditioned at an academy
[Bae Seongjae] 学院オーディションをされて
[Stella] That's right.
[Stella] そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] You got cast by 32 companies?
[Bae Seongjae] なんと32社からキャスティングを受けたんですか？
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Wow, 32 companies is like
[Bae Seongjae] はい。うわあ、これ32社だったらほとんどその
[Bae Seongjae] being drafted by all 32 teams in Major League Baseball, but you chose
[Bae Seongjae] アメリカ野球メジャーリーグで32チームがドラフトした感じですが、その中で
[Bae Seongjae] SM out of them? Yes, yes, that's right.
[Bae Seongjae] じゃあSMを選んだんですね？はい、はい、そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, what was your reason for choosing them?
[Bae Seongjae] あー、選んだ理由は
[Stella] Well, first I got
[Stella] その、一番最初に私が会社から
[Stella] cast by the company and then I wanted to audition for 2nd and 3rd rounds at companies
[Stella] キャスティングを受けて、私がちょっと2次3次オーディションを受けたい会社に
[Stella] that I was interested, but SM contacted me first with the acceptance news
[Stella] 話をしたんですが、一番最初にSMから連絡が来て合格の知らせが
[Stella] So I thought, ah, this is fate. I wanted to join SM anyway, and they
[Stella] だから、あ、これが運命だって。どうせSMに入りたかったのに一番
[Stella] contacted me first
[Stella] 先に連絡をくれたので
[Bae Seongjae] I'm thinking of making you do a World Cup tournament. So let me set up a bracket for the round of 32
[Bae Seongjae] 入ったらワールドカップをする考えはありましたか。じゃあとりあえず32強で私がトーナメント表を
[Bae Seongjae] I'll make one for you, so let's try a World Cup where you appeal to me. Make it to at least the semi-finals. Something like
[Bae Seongjae] 作ってあげるから、私にアピールすることでワールドカップを一回やってみましょう。4強まではとりあえず上がってきてください。そんな
[Bae Seongjae] that
[Bae Seongjae] こと
[Stella] It wasn't like that, I just really love SM's senior artists
[Stella] そんなことじゃなくて、私がSMの先輩方をすごく好きで
[Bae Seongjae] Ah wow, that's almost like real major
[Bae Seongjae] あ、これくらいならほぼ本当にメジャー
[Bae Seongjae] league level, like Ohtani class. Yes, it really was 32 teams.
[Bae Seongjae] リーグで言えば大谷級ですね。わあ、本当に32強でした。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, that's one more than Baskin-Robbins flavors, right? Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、アイスクリームより数字が一つ多いですね。そうでしょう？はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Sorry about that.
[Bae Seongjae] すみません。
[Stella] No, it's fine.
[Stella] いえ、はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Now, could you brag about your agency SM for us?
[Bae Seongjae] はい。では、所属事務所SMの自慢を一回してもらえるなら
[Yuha] Oh
[Yuha] おお
[Yuha] Wow
[Yuha] わあ
[Yuha] There's so much to brag about.
[Yuha] 自慢することすごく多いでしょう。
[Yuha] So much.
[Yuha] すごく多いでしょう。
[Yuha] Because our company loyalty is incredible
[Yuha] 愛社精神がものすごいので
[Yuha] First
[Yuha] まず
[Stella] First, our senior artists
[Stella] まず先輩方
[Stella] Our senior artists that we really respect and think are amazing
[Stella] 先輩方を私たちがすごく尊敬していて、すごいと思う先輩方
[Stella] Who are they all
[Stella] 誰々全部
[Bae Seongjae] It's hard to mention them all, right? Yes. Among them, if there's someone you've met recently
[Bae Seongjae] 全員挙げるのはちょっと難しいでしょう。はい。その中で最近会った方が
[Bae Seongjae] for the sake of the senior artists
[Bae Seongjae] いらっしゃるなら先輩方のために
[Yuha] Recently, Kim Heechul sunbae helped us a lot during variety show filming
[Yuha] 最近キム・ヒチョル先輩がバラエティ撮影の時にたくさん助けてくださって
[Bae Seongjae] We were so grateful. Oh, how did he help you?
[Bae Seongjae] すごく感謝でした。おお、何を助けてくださったんですか？
[Stella] Uh, he joked around a lot and talked to us
[Stella] あ、面白くいたずらもたくさんして、話しかけてくださって
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, it's a bit hard to spoil which program yet
[Bae Seongjae] あ、番組はまだちょっとネタバレはちょっとあれだし
[Yuha] Ah, but the article already came out - it's Knowing Bros
[Yuha] あ、もう記事が出たんですが「知ってるお兄さん」は
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, you appeared on Knowing Bros. Ah, yes
[Bae Seongjae] あ、知ってるお兄さんに出たんですね。あ、はい
[Bae Seongjae] Is there any song by SM senior artists that
[Bae Seongjae] そのダークダイ96さんがSM先輩の歌の
[Bae Seongjae] you'd like to cover? Uh
[Bae Seongjae] 中でカバーしたい曲がもしかしてありますか？あ
[Stella] Actually, we recently covered f(x) sunbae's Electric Shock at our fan meeting
[Stella] 実は私たちが最近ファンミーティングでf(x)先輩の「Electric Shock」っていうその歌を
[Stella] I've always wanted to do it since my trainee days, so it already had this kind of feeling
[Stella] カバーしたんですが、私が練習生の時からずっとやりたくて、もうちょっとこんな感じが
[Bae Seongjae] It's a masterpiece.
[Bae Seongjae] 名曲ですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, so you call it Electric Shock.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、Electric Shockと言うんですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. I used to call it Electric Shock
[Bae Seongjae] はい。私はElectric Shockと言ってたんですが
[Staff] Ah, yes.
[Staff] あ、はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, between this and Shock, something like this at the end
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ShockとShockって何か後ろに
[Bae Seongjae] if you remove that, it sounds kind of cool. Ah,
[Bae Seongjae] あるのを抜いた方がちょっとかっこいいですね。あ、
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, you recently had an SMTOWN concert. Uh, what was the most memorable moment?
[Bae Seongjae] あ、最近SMTOWNコンサートをやったんですが、あ、一番記憶に残る瞬間はいつですか？
[Stella] Uh, when do you remember? For me
[Stella] あ、私いつが記憶に残りますか？私は
[Stella] recently when I got to perform on stage with
[Stella] 最近少女時代のヒョヨン先輩と
[Stella] Girls' Generation's Hyoyeon sunbae, that was probably the most memorable for me. I see.
[Stella] 一緒にステージをすることになったんですが、その時が一番嬉しかったと思います。そうですね。
[Stella] Being able to perform together with such a senior
[Stella] 大先輩と今度一緒にステージを一緒にできるから
[Stella] I was so nervous but they were so kind to me, so it's a really happy memory.
[Stella] とても緊張もしたし、とてもよくしてくださって本当に幸せだった思い出があります。
[Bae Seongjae] You were born in '07, right?
[Bae Seongjae] 07年生だからそうですよね？
[Stella] Yes, that's right.
[Stella] はい。そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] In a way, you were born around when Girls' Generation was just starting their activities. Wow
[Bae Seongjae] ある意味、少女時代が本格的に今度活動を始める頃にお生まれになったんですね。いやー
[Bae Seongjae] That must really be overwhelming.
[Bae Seongjae] 本当に感慨深いでしょうね。
[Bae Seongjae] Any company seniors you've gotten close to? Someone you can say you're friends with?
[Bae Seongjae] 所属事務所の先輩でこうやって親しくなった方。でもこの方とは親しいって一度話せる。
[Speaker] Mm.
[Speaker] うーん。
[Yuha] Oh, Hyoyeon sunbaenim who we're close with.
[Yuha] あー、親しいヒョヨン先輩。
[Stella] Hyoyeon sunbaenim. Yes. Kim Heechul sunbaenim.
[Stella] ヒョヨン先輩。はい。キム・ヒチョル先輩。
[Stella] Heechul sunbaenim
[Stella] ヒチョル先輩
[Bae Seongjae] Those are the ones you can mention since you recently worked together.
[Bae Seongjae] そのくらいが今度最近一緒に何かをしたから、それでもお話しするのは大丈夫だと。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Now, next search term. '07-liners.
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、それでは次の検索ワード。'07-liners。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh. Ah, you two became adults this year,
[Bae Seongjae] おお。あ、お二人は今年成人になった
[Bae Seongjae] Born in 2007, '07-liner friends.
[Bae Seongjae] 2007年生まれの'07-liners同い年ですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, Park Gyeong-dong said the '07-liners became adults and finally went to PC rooms at night
[Bae Seongjae] あ、パク・キョンドンさんが'07-linersが成人になって夜間のPC房にやっと行ってきたと
[Bae Seongjae] Is there anything you want to try together as adults?
[Bae Seongjae] 成人として一緒にやってみたいことはありますか？
[Yuha] Oh, I want to try getting my driver's license.
[Yuha] あ、運転免許を一度取ってみたいです。
[Bae Seongjae] License already? Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] 免許をもう？はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, you want to get it quickly so you can drive somewhere on trips and stuff like that?
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ちょっと早めに取って、どうにか車を運転してどこか旅行に行きたいとか、そういうのがあってそうですか？
[Yuha] Yes. Even if I get my license, I probably won't have time, but still
[Yuha] はい。実際免許を取っても時間がない気がするんですが、それでも何か
[Yuha] I can get it when I turn 20, so I want to try
[Yuha] 20歳になったら取れるから、一回やってみて
[Bae Seongjae] Since you can get the qualification then.
[Bae Seongjae] 資格を取れますからね。
[Bae Seongjae] Anything else? Like maybe trying beer for the first time or something?
[Bae Seongjae] 他には何かありませんか？まあそれでも一度チメクをしてみたいとか、あるいは何か何かうーん
[Stella] That too, someday going to Han River and eating ramen there
[Stella] それもいつかは一度、漢江で、はい、漢江でラーメンも食べて
[Bae Seongjae] Eating ramen, that's great.
[Bae Seongjae] ラーメン食べて、いいですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Lucky 110 asks, "In your teens, is there something you'd want to say to your 20-year-old self"
[Bae Seongjae] ラッキー110さんが10代の私が20歳の私にもし言ってあげたい
[Bae Seongjae] something to say.
[Bae Seongjae] 言葉があるなら。
[Speaker] Mm
[Speaker] うーん
[Bae Seongjae] Shouldn't it be the other way around? If your 20-year-old self has something to say to your teenage self
[Bae Seongjae] 逆になるべきじゃないですか？20歳の私が10代の私に言ってあげたい言葉があるなら
[Bae Seongjae] To your younger self
[Bae Seongjae] 幼い頃の私に
[Yuha] Well, it wasn't that long ago, but
[Yuha] あーでも少し前だけど
[Yuha] Play more, have more fun
[Yuha] もっとたくさん遊べ、もっとたくさん遊んで
[Yuha] Enjoy more
[Yuha] 楽しめ、たくさん
[Bae Seongjae] Was there something you couldn't enjoy?
[Bae Seongjae] 何かちょっと楽しめなかったことがありますか？もしかして
[Yuha] Oh, that's
[Yuha] あ、それは
[Yuha] not it
[Yuha] そういうわけじゃないけど
[Yuha] That's not it, but just have more fun
[Yuha] そういうわけじゃないけど、もっと明るく遊んでうーん
[Bae Seongjae] In the chat someone said 'you made it,' someone said buy stocks
[Bae Seongjae] チャット欄に君は浮いたって、君は浮いたって言った方がいるし、株を
[Bae Seongjae] Someone said since you'll practice like crazy later,
[Bae Seongjae] 買えって言った方がいるし、あ、練習を死ぬほどやることになるから
[Bae Seongjae] play while you can. Ah, that's true. Once you enter the company, you have to practice incredibly hard
[Bae Seongjae] 遊んでおけって言った方もいるし。あ、そうですね。いつか今度会社にちゃんと入ってその時からは死ぬほど練習をしなければ
[Bae Seongjae] from then on.
[Bae Seongjae] ならないから。
[Bae Seongjae] You'll win nine rookie awards, so prepare your acceptance speech in advance. Oh.
[Bae Seongjae] 君、新人賞を9個もらうから事前に受賞感想を準備しておけ。あ。
[Bae Seongjae] Now, you two are the same age but have completely opposite MBTIs.
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、お二人は同い年だけどMBTIは真逆なんですね。
[Yuha] Yes. That's right. Exactly.
[Yuha] はい。そうです。そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Yuha, you're
[Bae Seongjae] ユハさんは
[Yuha] INTJ.
[Yuha] INTJ。
[Bae Seongjae] INTJ. And Stella, you're
[Bae Seongjae] INTJ。ステラさんは
[Yuha] I'm ENFP.
[Yuha] 私はENFP。
[Bae Seongjae] ENFP. Yes. Have you ever felt like "wow, we're really different"
[Bae Seongjae] ENFP。はい。ちょっとこうやって一緒に回ってて、あ、本当にだいぶ違うなって
[Bae Seongjae] when hanging out together?
[Bae Seongjae] 感じを受けたことありますか？
[Yuha] With Stella, I don't really think we're that different, but
[Yuha] ステラは別にそんなに違うって感じはしないけど、ちょっと
[Yuha] that's right.
[Yuha] そうですね。
[Yuha] Oh, how should I put it? She seems to have a bit of a fiery personality. Her style is, ah,
[Yuha] あ、どうかな？血の気質がちょっとある感じがします。スタイルは、あ、
[Bae Seongjae] Planning
[Bae Seongjae] 計画が
[Yuha] kind of impulsive, like
[Yuha] ちょっと直感的に
[Yuha] "Let's go buy this," or "Let's go eat that." She really likes that kind of thing, and I really like planning things
[Yuha] これ買いに行こう、これ食べに行こうって、そういうのすごく好きで、私はちょっと計画立てるのをすごく好んで
[Yuha] so that's kind of different.
[Yuha] るから、そういうのがちょっと違うかな。
[Bae Seongjae] You're both N types, and Yuha, are you more on the I side? Yes. It seems like
[Bae Seongjae] お二人ともNで、ユハさんはちょっとI寄りですか？はい。半々って
[Yuha] it's half and half, but still more I
[Yuha] 感じだけど、それでもI
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, Stella, are you definitely E? That's right.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ステラさんは確信のEですか？そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Are you T, Yuha? Yes
[Bae Seongjae] Tですか、ユハさん？はい
[Yuha] I'm T.
[Yuha] Tです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, so when you're talking, there are
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ちょっとじゃあ何か会話する時にちょっとその
[Bae Seongjae] still some cold moments sometimes? Right
[Bae Seongjae] それでも冷たい瞬間もあるんですか？そう
[Stella] Sometimes
[Stella] たまに
[Stella] But even though Yuha is totally T,
[Stella] でもあ、ユハは完全Tだけど
[Stella] she's really emotional and sensitive.
[Stella] すごく感性的で感性豊かなんです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, but still calm and composed, right.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、それでも冷静でしょ。
[Stella] So she empathizes well too, and I've never really felt like she's super T. And Stella, are you perfectly
[Stella] だから共感もよくしてくれるし、すごくTだって感じたことないかも。まだ ステラさんは完璧な
[Yuha] F? Uh, but I'm not perfectly either, sometimes
[Yuha] Fですか？え、でもまた完璧でもないし、たまに
[Bae Seongjae] she shows that side. Oh, sometimes like that. You both have a lot of half-and-half traits. Yes, yes
[Bae Seongjae] 姿が あ、たまにそうなんだ 半々が多いですね。お二人とも はいはい
[Bae Seongjae] Do you two '07-liners ever bicker about things like menu choices or something?
[Bae Seongjae] 07年生同士で何かこうやってぶつかることもありますか？メニュー選びとか何か
[Stella] But I feel like Haram and Yuha and I have never had any really big
[Stella] でも私はハラム、ユハとは何かすごく大きく喧嘩したことがない
[Stella] fights. Yes.
[Stella] 気がします。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Opposite personality types surprisingly don't fight much. I see.
[Bae Seongjae] 反対の性格同士が意外とあまり喧嘩しないんですよね。そうですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Now, the next keyword is piano, which is Yuha's keyword. You're a famous piano prodigy who's been playing since age six.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。じゃあ、次のキーワード ピアノ ユハさんのキーワードですが。6歳
[Bae Seongjae] who's been playing piano since age six.
[Bae Seongjae] の時からピアノを弾いた有名なピアノ英才です。
[Yuha] Mm.
[Yuha] うん。
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, how good were you?
[Bae Seongjae] や、どの程度実力ありましたか？
[Yuha] Uh, I competed in competitions every year to some extent
[Yuha] え、ある程度大会を毎年出てたんですけど
[Bae Seongjae] Cool.
[Bae Seongjae] コンクール？
[Yuha] Yes. From first grade in elementary school until about second, third grade in middle school
[Yuha] はい。小1から うん 中2、中3まで
[Yuha] I competed every year and
[Yuha] 毎年出てたんですけど、いつも
[Yuha] I think I always placed in the top rankings.
[Yuha] 順位内に入ってた気がします。
[Bae Seongjae] I see here, Chuncheon City National Music Competition Piano Division Elementary 1st Place.
[Bae Seongjae] 見たら春川市全国音楽コンクール ピアノ部門 小学部1位。
[Staff] Mm.
[Staff] うん。
[Bae Seongjae] Multiple piano competition awards in elementary school. Wow. But that piano performance
[Bae Seongjae] 小学校の時ピアノコンクール受賞経歴多数。いや。でもそのピアノ演奏
[Bae Seongjae] video and there's this comment.
[Bae Seongjae] 動画があるんですが、そのコメントがあるんですよ。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, someone named Potato F4 said they went to the same school and there was always 'Grand Prize Winner Yu Haram'
[Bae Seongjae] え〜、ジャガイモF4さんが同じ学校だったんですが、いつもピアノ学院の前に大賞ユハラム
[Bae Seongjae] posted in front of the piano academy.
[Bae Seongjae] って書いてありました。
[Staff] Wow
[Staff] うわあ
[Bae Seongjae] So when they heard you were debuting, they were like 'Oh, that kid who plays piano really well.'
[Bae Seongjae] それでデビューするって名前聞いた時に、あ〜あのピアノ上手い子だって思いました。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh
[Bae Seongjae] え
[Bae Seongjae] Right. Since your real name is Yu Haram. That's right.
[Bae Seongjae] そうですよね。本名が今ユハラムですから。そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] And someone said you seem to play the best among all the idols who claim to play piano.
[Bae Seongjae] そして今までピアノ弾くって言ってたアイドルの中で一番上手い感じだと。
[Stella] Oh right. She plays really well.
[Stella] あ、そうです。すごく上手なんです。
[Bae Seongjae] Have you seen her play? [Stella] I saw her once during trainee days and she played so
[Bae Seongjae] え、弾くの見ました？ [Stella] 練習生の時に一回見たんですけど、すっごく上手に
[Stella] well. I was really surprised.
[Stella] 弾くんですよ。それでびっくりしました。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, did you ever think like, while playing piano, that you'd
[Bae Seongjae] え〜、ちょっとこれ本当に私がそのピアノ弾きながらこっちの道で私が後で
[Bae Seongjae] become a pianist later on?
[Bae Seongjae] ピアニストになろう。そんな考えをしたこともありますか？
[Yuha] Yes. Originally my dream was to be a pianist, so I was preparing for arts high school entrance exams and stuff,
[Yuha] はい。元々はピアニストが夢だったので、芸高入試とかも
[Yuha] but after joining the company
[Yuha] 準備しようとしてたんですけど、会社に入ってから
[Yuha] I started thinking I should become an idol instead
[Yuha] ちょっとアイドルをやろうって思って
[Yuha] and here I am.
[Yuha] なった感じです。
[Bae Seongjae] Do you sometimes keep playing the keyboard so your skills don't get rusty?
[Bae Seongjae] たまにこうやって錆びないように続けて鍵盤をちょっと演奏したりするんですか？
[Yuha] Yes. Sometimes when I'm stressed, I play piano alone at the company.
[Yuha] はい。たまにストレス解消する時にこうやって会社で一人でピアノ弾いたりもして。
[Yuha] But I'm not as good as I used to be.
[Yuha] でも昔ほどじゃないですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Are you thinking about composing or anything like that later on?
[Bae Seongjae] 後でそれじゃあ何か作曲とかそういう方面も少し考えがありますか？
[Yuha] Oh. Yes. I really want to try composing and stuff.
[Yuha] あ、はい。すごく作曲とかやってみたいです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh. People ask what you've been doing instead of preparing piano for 'Ten', and you play piano to relieve stress.
[Bae Seongjae] え〜。ペテンピアノ準備もしないで何してるって言われるけど、ストレス解消のために
[Bae Seongjae] That's really good.
[Bae Seongjae] ピアノを弾くなんて。いいことですよね。本当に。
[Bae Seongjae] Now, the next search term is Canada
[Bae Seongjae] さ、そして次の検索ワードはカナダ
[Stella] Uh-oh. Mm.
[Stella] あはは。うん。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, this is Stella's keyword
[Bae Seongjae] あ、Stellaさんのキーワードが
[Bae Seongjae] Yes, when you were about five years old
[Bae Seongjae] はい、5歳の時ぐらいに
[Bae Seongjae] you immigrated to Vancouver, Canada
[Bae Seongjae] カナダのバンクーバーに移民に行かれてから
[Stella] Yes, that's right.
[Stella] はい、そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] and then came back to Korea, to Busan.
[Bae Seongjae] また釜山に韓国に逆移民で来たケースですね。
[Bae Seongjae] So you're definitely in charge of English for Hearts2Hearts?
[Bae Seongjae] Hearts2Heartsのそれじゃあ英語担当はほぼ絶対的に
[Stella] Ah, that's right.
[Stella] あ、そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Is English more comfortable for you, or Korean?
[Bae Seongjae] 英語が楽ですか、韓国語が楽ですか？
[Stella] I think English is still more comfortable for me.
[Stella] 私はまだ英語の方が楽だと思います。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, I see. So you dream in English too. Then
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そうですね。じゃあ夢見る時も英語で英語で夢見て。え〜それじゃあ
[Bae Seongjae] when you talk with your parents
[Bae Seongjae] ご両親と会話する時は
[Stella] Uh, when we lived in Canada we mixed both languages, but now that we're back in Korea
[Stella] え〜カナダに住んでた時はちょっと半々で混ぜてたんですけど、今韓国にまた来たので
[Stella] we mainly speak Korean now.
[Stella] 今は韓国語中心でやってる感じです。
[Bae Seongjae] Hey, then, what do you call it, in Canada it's hockey right? Ice hockey.
[Bae Seongjae] やあそれじゃあその何ていうかカナダといえばホッケーじゃないですか？アイスホッケー。
[Stella] That's right.
[Stella] そうですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Did you watch ice hockey and stuff?
[Bae Seongjae] え〜アイスホッケーもちょっと見たりしました？
[Stella] Not really. [Bae Seongjae] That's too bad. Yeah.
[Stella] え〜そうじゃなかったです。[Bae Seongjae] それは残念ですね。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] I recently watched ice hockey during the Winter Olympics
[Bae Seongjae] アイスホッケー私は少し前にその冬季オリンピックの
[Bae Seongjae] finals match between Canada and the US.
[Bae Seongjae] その決勝戦、カナダ対アメリカの試合を見ました。
[Stella] Oh really? Ah,
[Stella] あ本当ですか？あ、
[Bae Seongjae] Our Canadian girl, that match
[Bae Seongjae] カナダ人はその試合
[Stella] Do you like ice hockey?
[Stella] アイスホッケー好きですか？
[Stella] I'm gonna start liking ice hockey now. Yeah. I'll wear ice hockey clothes.
[Stella] アイスホッケーこれから好きになろうと思って。アイスホッケーの服着ます。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] If you want me to stop talking about stuff you're not curious about,
[Bae Seongjae] 興味のない話はするなって
[Bae Seongjae] just say you're sick of it. Yeah.
[Bae Seongjae] つまらないって言われたらやめますが。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] So you're from Canada, but your hometown is Ulsan and your parents live in Busan.
[Bae Seongjae] えっと、カナダ出身だけど故郷はえっと蔚山、ご両親は釜山にお住まいで。
[Bae Seongjae] So you sometimes slip into dialect.
[Bae Seongjae] それで方言がたまに出るって。
[Stella] Yeah, that's right.
[Stella] えっと、そうです。
[Stella] Yeah. It comes out without me knowing and the members always tease me like, "Why'd you
[Stella] えっと。私も知らずに出ちゃうんですけど、メンバーがいつも、あなた方言なんで
[Stella] use dialect?" I remember that.
[Stella] 出したの？ってからかわれた記憶があります。
[Bae Seongjae] What kind of dialect slips out sometimes? The ones you use often.
[Bae Seongjae] えっと。何が何がたまにこう飛び出すんですか？よく使う方言。
[Stella] But I don't even realize it's coming out
[Stella] でも私もちょっと私もちょっと知らずに出ちゃって
[Bae Seongjae] Uh
[Bae Seongjae] えっと
[Stella] We have YE-ON who's from Yangsan, our youngest, and when I talk with
[Stella] 今度私たちのYE-ONって子が梁山から来た子がいるんですけど末っ子がいるんですけど、その子と
[Stella] her, the dialect comes out a lot.
[Stella] 会話する時に方言がよく出る気がします。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, so it slips out when you meet someone from the same region. Yeah
[Bae Seongjae] あぁむしろその、ちょっと同郷の人に会うとすっと出ちゃうんですね。えっと
[Bae Seongjae] Can you say something? From the Yeongnam region?
[Bae Seongjae] 何か一言できるのありますか？嶺南地方の
[Bae Seongjae] Got anything you're confident with? [Stella] Unni, oppa, I love you.
[Bae Seongjae] 何か自信あるの？[Stella] お兄さんお姉さん愛してるって。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh,
[Bae Seongjae] えっと、
[Bae Seongjae] It came right out. And since you speak English well, you got the English narration
[Bae Seongjae] すぐ出ますね。そして英語がお上手で今回RUDEで英語ナレーション
[Bae Seongjae] killing part in RUDE, and everyone's going crazy saying it's super cute and cool.
[Bae Seongjae] キリングパートを担当したんですけど、これがすごく可愛くてクールだって大騒ぎでした。
[Bae Seongjae] Could you do that narration
[Bae Seongjae] もしかしてこれ無伴奏でナレーション
[Staff] Oh
[Staff] おお
[Bae Seongjae] part a cappella?
[Bae Seongjae] パートできますか？
[Staff] Of course.
[Staff] 当然でしょ。
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah. I watched the music video earlier and how should I put it? The feeling was really
[Bae Seongjae] はい。僕もさっきMV見たんですけど、えーっと何て言えばいいかな？この感じがすごく
[Bae Seongjae] special.
[Bae Seongjae] 特別でした。
[Bae Seongjae] Could we hear it?
[Bae Seongjae] 一回見せてもらえますか？
[Stella] Yes. You know what he said to me? He was
[Stella] はい。You know what he said to me? He was
[Stella] like, "You're so rude." And I was like,
[Stella] like, "You're so rude." And I was like,
[Stella] couldn't even
[Stella] couldn't even
[Bae Seongjae] Sounds like something from Disney or American TV shows with
[Bae Seongjae] ディズニーのそのを一回見たことがあるような、海外ドラマの
[Bae Seongjae] teenage girls. Thank you.
[Bae Seongjae] その10代の少女が出てくる感じでありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Could we try switching parts?
[Bae Seongjae] パート交代できますか？
[Yuha] Oh, let's see. I'll try it. I think I'll do well.
[Yuha] おお、見てみよう。やってみます。上手くやりそう。
[Bae Seongjae] Can you do it? I'll try the narration part.
[Bae Seongjae] できますか？ナレーションパートやってみます。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh.
[Bae Seongjae] えっと。
[Yuha] You know what he said to me? What?
[Yuha] You know what he said to me? What?
[Yuha] He was like, "You're so rude." And I was like, "Bo, does it
[Yuha] He was like, "You're so rude." And I was like, "Bo, does it
[Yuha] look like I could care? I couldn't even care."
[Yuha] look like I could care? I couldn't even care."
[Bae Seongjae] Wow,
[Bae Seongjae] わあ、
[Bae Seongjae] Someone said it got rustic.
[Bae Seongjae] 渋くなったって言ってる方もいますし。
[Staff] So Korean
[Staff] すごく韓国人らしく
[Bae Seongjae] Cute. They said now they can understand you. Oh, but you're really good at it too, Yuha.
[Bae Seongjae] かわいい。もう聞き取れるようになりましたって言ってます。あ、でもすごく上手ですね、ユハさんも。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Great. Truly a global group.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。いいですね。さすがグローバルグループです。
[Bae Seongjae] Okay, so our time is almost up for Part 1,
[Bae Seongjae] はい。それでは、もう1部の時間になってしまったので
[Bae Seongjae] so we'll come back in Part 2 and chat with you two again.
[Bae Seongjae] 2部に戻って来て、また二人とお話ししていきます。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Not too hard, right?
[Bae Seongjae] あんまり難しくないでしょう？
[Stella] It's so fun.
[Stella] すごく楽しいです。
[Bae Seongjae] Time flies, right?
[Bae Seongjae] 時間あっという間でしょう？
[Stella] Yeah.
[Stella] はい。
[Staff] Did you go to an English kindergarten?
[Staff] 英語の幼稚園出身なんですか？
[Yuha] Huh?
[Yuha] はい？
[Yuha] Oh, no.
[Yuha] あ、違います。
[Staff] Then why are you so good at it?
[Staff] 違うのになんで上手なんですか？
[Stella] Yeah. But she's really good at English.
[Stella] はい。でも英語がすごく上手なんです。
[Bae Seongjae] Exactly
[Bae Seongjae] そうですよね
[Stella] She's really good with languages
[Stella] 言語がすごく得意で
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, but that pronunciation is almost native-level, really
[Bae Seongjae] わあ、でもほとんどネイティブの発音で本当に
[Bae Seongjae] Really like a teenage girl from American TV shows
[Bae Seongjae] 本当に完全にアメドラに出てくる10代の少女の
[Yuha] Thank you.
[Yuha] ありがとうございます。
[Yuha] So you watched that? [Bae Seongjae] Oh, this is something I ordered from overseas myself
[Yuha] これは、じゃあそれ見たんですか？ [Bae Seongjae] あ、これは僕が別途海外直輸入したんですが
[Bae Seongjae] It's ice hockey gear.
[Bae Seongjae] アイスホッケー用品です。
[Yuha] This team exists
[Yuha] このチームがあるんですが
[Bae Seongjae] This is that Minnesota... Minneso... yeah
[Bae Seongjae] これはそのミネソタ・ミネソータ　はい
[Stella] Oh you're doing well, Minnesota
[Stella] あ、上手ですね、ミネソタ
[Bae Seongjae] Kind of oh
[Bae Seongjae] ちょっと　おお
[Bae Seongjae] This was a unique gesture, oh
[Bae Seongjae] これ特異なジェスチャーでしたね　おお
[Stella] No no
[Stella] いやいや
[Bae Seongjae] Uh
[Bae Seongjae] え
[Stella] Oh you look cool
[Stella] え、かっこいいですね
[Bae Seongjae] Thank you
[Bae Seongjae] ありがとうございます
[Bae Seongjae] Uh Vancouver, so when did you move there? [Stella] Me, in 2013
[Bae Seongjae] あ、バンクーバー、それじゃあいつ移住されたんですか？ [Stella] 私　2013年度
[Stella] I went when I was five
[Stella] 5歳の時に行って
[Stella] lived there for 11 years then came back to Korea
[Stella] 11年間住んでまた韓国に戻って来ました
[Bae Seongjae] Vancouver, I went there first. I went in 2010 to cover the Winter Olympics
[Bae Seongjae] バンクーバー、僕の方が先に行きましたね。僕は2010年に冬季オリンピック中継で
[Bae Seongjae] Hmm
[Bae Seongjae] うーん
[Bae Seongjae] Strange sense of competition
[Bae Seongjae] 微妙な競争心
[Stella] Oh this is all being heard, right? Yeah.
[Stella] あ、これ全部聞こえてるんですよね？　はい。
[Stella] Ah. Uh. Hello.
[Stella] あ。え。こんにちは。
[Bae Seongjae] Hmm. Are you telling the junior to bow down? Yeah. Being
[Bae Seongjae] うーん。後輩は土下座しろと言ってますか？　はい。歳が
[Bae Seongjae] old is nice, they say.
[Bae Seongjae] 多くて羨ましいって言ってます。
[Bae Seongjae] Everyone, you're now with Bae Seongjae's TEN, with the lively and bold girl group
[Bae Seongjae] 皆さんは今、ペ・ソンジェのTEN　新曲RUDEで戻って来た溌剌として堂々たるガールズグループ
[Bae Seongjae] Hearts2Hearts' '07-liners Yuha and Stella, the Nutella duo, who came back with their new song RUDE!
[Bae Seongjae] Hearts2Heartsの07年生、ユハ、Stella、合わせてNutellaお二人と一緒に
[Bae Seongjae] We were doing keyword talk. Yeah. This time's keyword is
[Bae Seongjae] います。僕たちはキーワードトークをしていましたが。はい。今回のキーワードは
[Bae Seongjae] all-rounder. It's Yuha's keyword - she's a hexagon player all-rounder member who's good at dancing, singing, broadcasting, everything.
[Bae Seongjae] オールラウンダーです。ユハさんのキーワードで、ダンス歌放送全て
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, besides dancing and singing, you're really good at
[Bae Seongjae] 上手な六角形プレーヤー オールラウンダーメンバーなんですよ。あ、ダンス歌以外にも
[Bae Seongjae] so many other things. What else
[Bae Seongjae] 上手なことがすごく多いんですよね。どんな
[Bae Seongjae] are you good at? [Yuha] I'm really good at mental math.
[Bae Seongjae] ことをまた上手にされるんですか [Yuha] 私はあ、暗算が早く上手で。
[Bae Seongjae] Mental math?
[Bae Seongjae] 暗算？
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah. Uh, then what's 78 times 56?
[Bae Seongjae] はい。あ、それじゃあ78×56
[Yuha] Ah, I can't do stuff like that [Bae Seongjae] Then what about addition?
[Yuha] あ、こういうのはできません [Bae Seongjae] じゃあ何？足し算で？
[Yuha] I look at license plates
[Yuha] 私はその車のナンバープレートを見て
[Bae Seongjae] Mm-hmm
[Bae Seongjae] うん
[Yuha] and
[Yuha] あ
[Yuha] use the four basic operations to quickly make 24, but it's kinda hard
[Yuha] 四則演算をして24を素早く作れるんですが、これがちょっと難しいです
[Bae Seongjae] You look at those seven numbers on the license plate?
[Bae Seongjae] 車のナンバープレートのその数字7個を見て？
[Yuha] I look at four numbers
[Yuha] 4個を見て
[Bae Seongjae] The last four digits
[Bae Seongjae] 後ろの4桁を見て
[Yuha] I can quickly make 24 using the four basic operations.
[Yuha] 四則演算をして24を素早く作れます。
[Stella] She's really good at it. But
[Stella] 本当に上手なんです。でも
[Bae Seongjae] That's genius-level stuff, right? Uh, multiplying and subtracting to make 24
[Bae Seongjae] それって何の天才的な話ですか？あ、掛け算引き算をして24を、あ
[Bae Seongjae] So like
[Bae Seongjae] それじゃあ何
[Bae Seongjae] if the number is 3-3-8-6
[Bae Seongjae] 3 3 8 6みたいな番号だ。
[Yuha] 3-3-8-6. Then 3 times 3 equals 9, 9 minus 6 equals 3, 8 times 3 equals
[Yuha] 3 3 8 6だ。それなら3×3=9、9-6=3。8×3=
[Yuha] 24
[Yuha] 24
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, this is really unique.
[Bae Seongjae] わあ、これは本当に珍しいですね。
[Stella] Right?
[Stella] でしょう？
[Bae Seongjae] How do you... but why are you so obsessed with 24? Can you do other numbers too?
[Bae Seongjae] どうしてこれを、でもなぜずっと24にそのこだわりを持ってるんですか？他の数字もできますか？もしかして？
[Yuha] No, I can't.
[Yuha] いいえ。できません。
[Yuha] Just 24.
[Yuha] 24。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, making 24 is like a hobby.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、24作りがちょっと趣味かな。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh. Uh, but that's really fascinating.
[Bae Seongjae] あ。あ、でもすごく不思議だ。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, you're really fast. Then what about 7-8-9-2?
[Bae Seongjae] あ、本当に早いね。それじゃあ7 8 9 2
[Bae Seongjae] 7-8-9-2
[Bae Seongjae] 7 8 9 2
[Yuha] These numbers
[Yuha] この数字が
[Bae Seongjae] I should show you the numbers. 7-8-9-2
[Bae Seongjae] 数字を見せてあげないといけないんだな。7 8 9 2
[Yuha] 7-8-9-2, there are numbers that don't work.
[Yuha] 7 8 9 2、これもできない数字があるんですよ。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, you can immediately calculate which ones don't work. This one doesn't work
[Bae Seongjae] あ、できないのがすぐまた計算で出てくるんですね。これはできない
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, amazing. Oh
[Bae Seongjae] おお、不思議だ。おお
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, then do you have good memory too? [Yuha] Yes, yes. Uh, when fans come once,
[Bae Seongjae] やあ、それじゃあ記憶力も良いんですか？もしかして？ [Yuha] はい、はい。あ、ファンの方々が一度いらっしゃったら
[Yuha] I remember almost all of them well
[Yuha] ほとんど全部こんな風によく覚えていて
[Bae Seongjae] Their faces
[Bae Seongjae] 顔を
[Yuha] Yeah. I remember faces well
[Yuha] はい。顔をよく覚えていて
[Bae Seongjae] All those fans
[Bae Seongjae] そんなに多くのファンを
[Yuha] Yeah. I think so.
[Yuha] はい。そんな感じです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh,
[Bae Seongjae] おお、
[Yuha] Like with license plates too, once I see them I'm like 'I've seen that car before'
[Yuha] ちょっとその車のナンバープレートも一度見たらちょっと見たことある車だ。こんなこんな風に
[Bae Seongjae] You remember cars you've seen before? Wow, that kind of memory is like
[Bae Seongjae] 見たことある車を、やあ、そのこんな記憶力はほとんどまあ
[Bae Seongjae] investigator level, right? Investigators, police officers, detectives - you should work in the military
[Bae Seongjae] 捜査官でしょう？捜査官、警察官、こんな方々、刑事をしないといけない、はい。軍隊
[Bae Seongjae] MP work, I can see that.
[Bae Seongjae] 歩哨もよく分かりますけど。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, do you remember names quickly too then?
[Bae Seongjae] おお、名前もそれなら すぐ覚えますか？
[Yuha] Yes. If I can match it with a face, I remember well.
[Yuha] はい。顔とマッチすれば よく覚えます。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, so once you match a face with a name like that, you usually remember
[Bae Seongjae] あ、顔とこうやってぴったり名前をマッチさせれば だいたい覚える
[Bae Seongjae] it. Wow, I see.
[Bae Seongjae] んですね。いや〜、そうなんですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, speaking of TMI, you debuted on February 24th.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、TMI思い出したんですけど、2月24日にデビューされたじゃないですか。
[Bae Seongjae] So getting the 24th right isn't just a coincidence
[Bae Seongjae] だから24日に合わせているわけじゃなくて
[Stella] That's right. Right. Correct. Correct.
[Stella] そうです。そうですね。そうです。そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. You remember my name, right? Seongjae.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。僕の名前覚えてくださいね？ソンジェ。
[Bae Seongjae] Bae Seongjae, yes. Please memorize it once. When you come back in a few years,
[Bae Seongjae] ペ・ソンジェです。はい。一度覚えてください。後で何年か後にまた来られた
[Bae Seongjae] I'll test you on it. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] 時に一度テストしてみます。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, some people have called me Seo Seongjae, An Seongjae, and someone said the Seongjae type is the worst.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ソ・ソンジェと言われた方がいて、アン・ソンジェと言われた方、ソンジェ類最悪と言われた方がいて。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, and I see you're good at Chinese.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そういえば中国語がお上手ですね。
[Yuha] Ah, that's right. Uh,
[Yuha] あ、そうです。えっと、
[Bae Seongjae] What's your skill level? Are you native? [Yuha] No, not that level, just kinda
[Bae Seongjae] どのくらいの実力？ネイティブですか？[Yuha] いえ。そこまではなくて、ちょっと
[Yuha] I like watching Chinese dramas and stuff, so I learned a bit during trainee days too, so I can do just a little bit.
[Yuha] 中国ドラマを見たりするのが好きで、練習生の時も少し習ったりして、本当にちょっとだけできます。
[Bae Seongjae] Which drama did you watch a lot?
[Bae Seongjae] どんなドラマよく見ました？
[Yuha] My favorite one is a drama called 'Tutuzhangfuzhu'.
[Yuha] 一番好きなのは「突突蒋布珠」というドラマを見ました。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, then how about greeting once in Chinese
[Bae Seongjae] あ、それなら中国語で一度挨拶を一度
[Yuha] Ah
[Yuha] あ
[Bae Seongjae] Or try some drama lines? Or
[Bae Seongjae] ドラマのセリフを一度やってみましょうか？それとも
[Yuha] Hmm
[Yuha] うーん
[Yuha] Drama lines?
[Yuha] ドラマのセリフですか？
[Yuha] Yes. How about
[Yuha] はい。どんな
[Bae Seongjae] Any part from that drama, a dramatic part would be even better.
[Bae Seongjae] そのそのドラマに出てくる何か部分でも、劇的な部分だともっといいです。
[Yuha] Let's go.
[Yuha] 行こう。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。
[Yuha] Uh. Uh. Long se
[Yuha] あ。あ。冷死了
[Bae Seongjae] What does that mean? "I'm hungry"? [Yuha] "I'm freezing to death."
[Bae Seongjae] 何ですか？お腹すいた。[Yuha] 寒くて死にそうだ。
[Bae Seongjae] Why did I think 'I'm hungry'? Aha, I see. Then how about
[Bae Seongjae] 僕なんでお腹すいたって思ったんだろう？あはそうなんですね。それならどうやって
[Bae Seongjae] greeting us in Chinese
[Bae Seongjae] 中国語で僕たち
[Bae Seongjae] once
[Bae Seongjae] 挨拶を一度
[Yuha] Uh,
[Yuha] あ 大家好
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, somehow it sounds nice even just listening. What does it mean?
[Bae Seongjae] あ 何か聞いても気分がいいですね。何て言ってるんですか？
[Yuha] Please listen to our new song RUDE a lot.
[Yuha] 僕たちの新曲RUDEをたくさん聞いてください。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, thank you. Really? Uh, you're really good at it. And
[Bae Seongjae] あ ありがとうございます。そうなんですか？あ 本当にお上手ですね。そして
[Bae Seongjae] is there anything else you're uniquely good at?
[Bae Seongjae] また もし その 特に得意なことが
[Bae Seongjae] Going down stairs quickly? What's this? Going down stairs fast? Jumping down
[Bae Seongjae] 階段を早く降りる？これ何ですか？階段を早く降りる？一度に飛んで
[Bae Seongjae] in one go? Or going tap-tap-tap? [Yuha] I'm good at both.
[Bae Seongjae] ジャンプで行くんですか？それともタタタって行くんですか？[Yuha] どっちも得意です。
[Yuha] I can jump down two steps at a time
[Yuha] 2段ずつ飛んで降りることもできるし
[Yuha] or like teleportation, just like this
[Yuha] 縮地法みたいにこうやってぱっと
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, like teleportation going tap-tap-tap too.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、縮地法みたいにタタタって行ったりもして。
[Yuha] Yes.
[Yuha] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] But if there were, say, ten-step stairs,
[Bae Seongjae] でももし何か10段くらいの階段があったら。
[Yuha] Then I'd skip about five steps at a time.
[Yuha] それなら5段ずつ飛んで降りるんです。
[Bae Seongjae] Five steps at a time. Ah, you divide it in half, that's calculated too.
[Bae Seongjae] 5段ずつ。あ、きっちり二等分して、それも計算されてるんですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, someone said to be careful with your joints
[Bae Seongjae] えっと、関節に気をつけろって言ってる方がいて
[Bae Seongjae] You gotta be careful with your joints. Yeah. And then, have any members
[Bae Seongjae] 関節気をつけないといけないですね。はい。で、その階段を速く降りるのをメンバーが
[Bae Seongjae] witnessed you going down stairs fast?
[Bae Seongjae] 目撃したことありますか？
[Stella] Oh. Ah when we were trainees preparing for debut, we said let's all exercise together, so we did stair
[Stella] あ。私たち練習生でデビュー準備してる時、みんなで運動しようって言って階段
[Stella] climbing up and down, and Yuha was always super fast at it.
[Stella] 上り下りをしたんですけど、いつもユハがめちゃくちゃ速くやってたんですよ。
[Yuha] Yeah. I think I got good at it through that. Going down stairs quickly. Yeah.
[Yuha] はい。それをやりながらちょっと覚えた気がします。階段を速く降りるの。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] But stairs, that's about having a feel for it too, right? You gotta match that step rhythm
[Bae Seongjae] 階段もでも、それも感覚ですからね。そうでしょ？こうやってタタタってそのステップを合わせないといけないし
[Yuha] Yeah. Yeah. And you can't just squeeze your way down the stairs, you gotta
[Yuha] はい。はい。あと、ちょっと階段をこうやってただ普通に降りちゃダメで、ちょっと
[Yuha] bend your legs diagonally and place your feet like this
[Yuha] 足を斜めに曲げて足をこうやって
[Yuha] Pro tip
[Yuha] 裏技
[Bae Seongjae] Then we should make this an ISAC event, right? Stairway to Heaven
[Bae Seongjae] じゃあ、もうアイドル陸上大会の種目を作らないといけないでしょう。そうでしょ？階段、天国の階段
[Bae Seongjae] event where you go down fast and up fast. You walk like a sage.
[Bae Seongjae] 種目を作って、えっと速く降りて速く上がってこれをやらないといけないんですね。仙人みたいに歩くなって
[Bae Seongjae] Someone said that. Yeah. Ah, and also anything else you're good at that you can
[Bae Seongjae] 言ってる方がいて、はい。あ、それと、他に得意なこと、アピールできるこれ
[Bae Seongjae] show off.
[Bae Seongjae] ちょっと押し出せる。
[Yuha] Show off.
[Yuha] 押し出せる。
[Yuha] Yeah.
[Yuha] うん。
[Yuha] What else is there? Hmm. Things I'm good at.
[Yuha] 他に何があるかな？うーん。得意な、得意なこと。
[Yuha] Hmm.
[Yuha] うーん。これ
[Yuha] That's about it.
[Yuha] くらいです。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, listener doyukseongje said Yuha is good at four-character idiom quizzes, so I'd like to try that.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ドユクソンジェさんがユハが四字熟語クイズが得意だって言ってるので、やってみたらいいと思います。
[Bae Seongjae] Are you good with four-character idioms?
[Bae Seongjae] 四字熟語得意ですか？
[Yuha] Oh, let me try. [Bae Seongjae] Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, so four-character idioms.
[Yuha] えっと、一回やってみます。[Bae Seongjae] はい。はい。はい。じゃあ、四字熟語。
[Yuha] Hmm.
[Yuha] うーん。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh. Gojin
[Bae Seongjae] えっと。苦尽
[Yuha] Gamrae
[Yuha] 甘来
[Bae Seongjae] Gyeol-ja
[Bae Seongjae] 結者
[Yuha] Haeji
[Yuha] 解之
[Bae Seongjae] Oh
[Bae Seongjae] おお
[Bae Seongjae] Gwayu
[Bae Seongjae] 過猶
[Yuha] Bulgup
[Yuha] 不及
[Bae Seongjae] Seolsang
[Bae Seongjae] 雪上
[Yuha] Gasang
[Yuha] 加霜
[Bae Seongjae] Oh
[Bae Seongjae] おお
[Bae Seongjae] Ipchun
[Bae Seongjae] 立春
[Yuha] Ipchun?
[Yuha] 立春？
[Yuha] Chosang (Give me a hint for the initials)
[Yuha] 初声？（初声ヒントください）
[Bae Seongjae] Uh demanding it right away, confidently. Yeah. D-sound memory
[Bae Seongjae] えっと、すぐ要求するんですか？堂々と？ㄷ ㄱ
[Yuha] D-sound memory? [Stella] Look at the comments [Yuha] Daegil?
[Yuha] ディグッ キオク？[Stella] コメント見て見て [Yuha] 大吉？
[Bae Seongjae] Hmm. Ah, Ipchun Daegil. Ah, this is kind of old culture so you might not
[Bae Seongjae] うーん。あ、立春大吉。あ、これはけっこう昔の文化だから知らないかも
[Bae Seongjae] know it. In the old days, like during the Joseon period or even recently at
[Bae Seongjae] しれないですね。昔は昔、朝鮮時代とか最近でも何か韓屋みたいな
[Bae Seongjae] traditional houses, they'd put up 'Ipchun Daegil' on the gate in spring.
[Bae Seongjae] ところは大門に立春大吉って春に貼ったりしてました。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, then Hamheung
[Bae Seongjae] えっと、じゃあ咸興
[Yuha] Chasa.
[Yuha] 差使。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh,
[Bae Seongjae] おお、
[Stella] Wow.
[Stella] わあ。
[Bae Seongjae] I was thinking naengmyeon earlier.
[Bae Seongjae] 僕はさっき冷麺だと思ったんですけど。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, then Stella, give it a try.
[Bae Seongjae] え、じゃあStellaさん一回。
[Stella] Ah, I
[Stella] あ、私は
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Uh, four-character quiz. You can say anything for this. As long as it makes sense.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。え、4文字クイズ。これは何でもいいです。言葉になればいいです。
[Stella] Ah, got it.
[Stella] あ、分かりました。
[Bae Seongjae] Chadol
[Bae Seongjae] チャドル
[Stella] Baegi.
[Stella] パギ。
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Easy, right? Comfortable, right? Uh, shoulder.
[Bae Seongjae] 簡単でしょ？楽でしょ？え、肩。
[Stella] What?
[Stella] え？
[Bae Seongjae] Shoulder.
[Bae Seongjae] 肩。
[Stella] Shoulder.
[Stella] 肩。
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah.
[Bae Seongjae] うん。
[Stella] Say it quick.
[Stella] 早く言って。
[Yuha] Friend.
[Yuha] 同志。
[Stella] Friend.
[Stella] 同志。
[Stella] Right.
[Stella] 正解。
[Bae Seongjae] Bank.
[Bae Seongjae] 銀行。
[Stella] Bank? Deposit!
[Stella] 銀行？入金！
[Bae Seongjae] That works. That works. Right. That's what matters most, right? Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] 言葉になります。なりますよ。それが一番大事でしょ？はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, impossible?
[Bae Seongjae] え、不可？
[Stella] Impossible relationship.
[Stella] 不可能。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, good.
[Bae Seongjae] お、いいですね。
[Stella] Uh, I think I did well just now. [Bae Seongjae] Waist?
[Stella] え、うまくいった気がする。今。[Bae Seongjae] 腰？
[Stella] Waist band
[Stella] 腰ベルト
[Bae Seongjae] Waist band
[Bae Seongjae] 腰ベルト
[Bae Seongjae] What we were expecting was hurricane but
[Bae Seongjae] 僕らが期待してたのはハリケーンだったんですけど
[Bae Seongjae] if you pronounce it well, hurricane
[Bae Seongjae] 発音をうまくやってくれるかと思って、ハリケーン
[Bae Seongjae] O-cane
[Bae Seongjae] ケーン
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, fortune
[Bae Seongjae] え、四柱
[Stella] Fortune telling
[Stella] 四柱占い
[Bae Seongjae] Fortune telling
[Bae Seongjae] 四柱占い
[Stella] This is right, right? But doing it is right, right?
[Stella] これが正解でしょ？やるのが正解でしょ？
[Bae Seongjae] Right. Yes, that's right. I was thinking of fortune and destiny too. Earlier with bank,
[Bae Seongjae] 正解。はい、正解です。四柱八字を考えてたのもあるし。さっき銀行は
[Bae Seongjae] I was thinking of ginkgo tree. Then, bari
[Bae Seongjae] 銀杏の木を考えてたし。じゃあバリ
[Stella] Bari?
[Stella] バリ？
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah.
[Bae Seongjae] うん。
[Bae Seongjae] Bari
[Bae Seongjae] バリ
[Stella] Barista.
[Stella] バリスタ。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh. This
[Bae Seongjae] え、これ
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, Stella seems to pick up on the English words well.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、Stellaさんは少し英語系がよく聞こえるみたいですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, good. Barista. Bulga.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、いいですね。バリスタ。不可。
[Stella] Bulgasaui.
[Stella] 不可思議。
[Bae Seongjae] Bulgasaui. Oh,
[Bae Seongjae] 不可思議。おお、
[Bae Seongjae] Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] We wrote 'bulga' but 'bulgasaui' works too. Correct.
[Bae Seongjae] 私たちは불가って書いてますが不可思議でも正解ですね。正解。
[Bae Seongjae] Bulgasari is a creature and bulgasaui is like, uh, something really mysterious in human history
[Bae Seongjae] ヒトデは生物で、不可思議はもう、すごくこういうことが人類史の
[Bae Seongjae] Mystery, that kind of feeling. Mystery
[Bae Seongjae] ミステリーみたいな感じ。ミステリー
[Bae Seongjae] Mystery-ari, if you listen casually
[Bae Seongjae] ミステリアスこれを適当に聞くと
[Bae Seongjae] Uh
[Bae Seongjae] あ
[Bae Seongjae] Good. Yes. Now then, next
[Bae Seongjae] いいですね。はい。じゃあ次は
[Bae Seongjae] Search term 'Gorgeous Snobby Girl'
[Bae Seongjae] 検索語「ゴージャス気取り屋」
[Bae Seongjae] I rolled my pronunciation without realizing it.
[Bae Seongjae] 私も知らずに発音を巻いちゃいましたね。
[Stella] Yes
[Stella] はい
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, this is a nickname that member Ian made for Stella. How does it feel?
[Bae Seongjae] あ、メンバーのIanさんが作ってくれたStellaさんの愛称ですが、どんな感じですか？
[Stella] Yes. Uh, when I speak English I kinda go 'gorgeous'
[Stella] はい。あ、もう私が英語をする時にちょっとゴージャス
[Stella] while being a bit snobby, so Ian said I'm like a gorgeous snobby girl.
[Stella] って言いながらちょっと気取ってるって言われて、Ianが私にゴージャス気取り屋みたいだって。
[Bae Seongjae] Gorgeous snobby girl.
[Bae Seongjae] ゴージャス気取り屋だって。
[Stella] Yes. It's embarrassing.
[Stella] はい。恥ずかしいですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, you have that cat-like look, right? Yes. But
[Bae Seongjae] あ、これはちょっとその猫顔ですしそうでしょ？はい。でも
[Bae Seongjae] rather than being snobby, you're actually full of aegyo.
[Bae Seongjae] 気取り屋じゃなくて実際は愛嬌っ子だって。
[Stella] That's right.
[Stella] そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Right. Uh.
[Bae Seongjae] そうでしょ。あ。
[Bae Seongjae] Why? Why? Why? Have you ever fallen victim to her aegyo by any chance?
[Bae Seongjae] なんで？なんで？なんで？愛嬌にやられたことありますか、もしかして？
[Yuha] Ah, but she's always like this. Lots of aegyo
[Yuha] あ、でもいつもこう。愛嬌多くて
[Yuha] Always like this.
[Yuha] いつもこうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, I just got that T vs F feeling. Someone said 'Stella kitty' is so
[Bae Seongjae] あ、今なんかTとFみたいな感じがしました。「テル猫ちゃん」すごく
[Bae Seongjae] cute. Seohee said Stella's first impression was hot girl, personality was
[Bae Seongjae] 可愛いって言った方がいて。ソヒさんがStellaの第一印象がホットガール、性格は
[Bae Seongjae] cool girl, but how did you become full of aegyo now? What happened in between?
[Bae Seongjae] クールガールだったのに今はどうして愛嬌っ子になったんですか？その間何かあったんでしょうか？
[Stella] But when I first joined SM, the members all said I had this really
[Stella] でも私が初めてもうSMに入社した時、メンバーたちがみんなすごくちょっと
[Stella] hot girl image. Back then I didn't really think of it that way, but
[Stella] ホットガールイメージだって言ってました。その時私はちょっとそう思わなかったんですが
[Stella] thinking about it now, I was totally a hot girl.
[Stella] 今思うと完全にホットガールだったと思います。
[Stella] Somehow I kinda became like this
[Stella] どうやってちょっともうこうやって
[Bae Seongjae] Ah yes. Everyone's saying you're so pretty. How often do the members witness Stella's
[Bae Seongjae] あ、はい。今みんなすごく可愛いって、そのどうやってメンバーたちが目撃したStella
[Bae Seongjae] aegyo? Uh
[Bae Seongjae] さんの愛嬌をよく見るようになりますか？あ
[Yuha] Often, often. She keeps putting her hand on her chin
[Yuha] よく、よく、ずっとこうやって手を顎に
[Yuha] and keeps making 'hmph' sounds like that
[Yuha] 当ててずっと「ふん」とかこういう音を出すんですが
[Yuha] She does it often.
[Yuha] よくそうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, can you two reenact that situation? Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、二人でちょっと再現できますか？はい。その状況。
[Stella] Uh yes
[Stella] あ、はい
[Stella] Mm
[Stella] ん
[Stella] Oh yes, thank you.
[Stella] ああ、ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, totally a T moment
[Bae Seongjae] やあ、ほんと完全にTモーメント
[Bae Seongjae] Breathing in through the nose. Yes. Besides 'gorgeous snobby girl,' there's also
[Bae Seongjae] 鼻で息を吸い込む。はい。ゴージャス気取り屋以外に「Sstobbi」という
[Bae Seongjae] a nickname called 'Sstobbi.'
[Bae Seongjae] 愛称もありますね。
[Bae Seongjae] What does this mean? [Stella] Haram made this one up
[Bae Seongjae] これはどんな意味ですか？[Stella] これもうHaramが付けてくれたもので
[Yuha] It means 'Stella's sulking again'.
[Yuha] 「ステラまた拗ねた」という意味なんです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, do you sulk a lot?
[Bae Seongjae] あー、よく拗ねるんですか？
[Yuha] She really sulks like ten times a day
[Yuha] 本当に1日に10回くらい拗ねて
[Stella] No I don't.
[Stella] 違います。
[Bae Seongjae] Like when you act cute but the members don't respond, you might sulk a little. Yeah.
[Bae Seongjae] ちょっと甘えたのにメンバーが受け取ってくれないと少し拗ねることもありますよね。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Is it like things where you think 'that's worth sulking over'?
[Bae Seongjae] そんなことでも拗ねる？っていうようなこと？
[Yuha] Like someone ate the fruit she ordered for herself. Stuff like that.
[Yuha] なんか自分が注文したフルーツを自分が食べた。こういうこと。
[Stella] Ah but she shares it well though.
[Stella] あー、でもよく食べるじゃないですか。
[Yuha] Right. It all works out in the end, but at first she definitely sulks no matter what.
[Yuha] そうです。結局はうまく解決はしますが、最初は絶対まず拗ねるみたいです。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, sulk first. Well, if I ordered fruit and someone else ate it, that's worth getting upset over
[Bae Seongjae] あー、とりあえず拗ねて。あー、フルーツを私が注文したのに他の人が食べたら腹立つこと
[Bae Seongjae] isn't it?
[Bae Seongjae] じゃないですか？
[Yuha] Ah, isn't that worth sulking over?
[Yuha] あー、拗ねることじゃないですか？
[Stella] That's right. Thank you.
[Stella] そうです。ありがとう。
[Bae Seongjae] Right. That's worth sulking over. [Stella] Ah really, so our members all just
[Bae Seongjae] そうですよね。それは拗ねて当然ですよね。[Stella] あー、本当にそれで私たちメンバーがみんなただもう
[Stella] eat it too
[Stella] 私も食べるから
[Stella] so I'm the only one who ends up sulking sometimes.
[Stella] 私だけひとりでちょっと拗ねる時があるみたい。
[Bae Seongjae] That's worth sulking over. Right? Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] それは拗ねて当然ですよね。そうでしょ？はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Someone said 'Bae Seongjae Sstupit'
[Bae Seongjae] ペ・ソンジェもスットッピだと言ってる方がいて
[Yuha] Ah, you really love food.
[Yuha] あー、食べることがすごく好きなんですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah right. Ah
[Bae Seongjae] あー、そうですね。あー
[Bae Seongjae] When I said Sstupit, they told me to 'stop eat'.
[Bae Seongjae] スットッピと言ったら、私のことをストップeatと言われて。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh I see. Haeeun Gongsa님 asked for a balance game. Forever in charge of aegyo
[Bae Seongjae] あー、そうですか。ヘウン公使様がバランスゲームしてください。一生愛嬌
[Bae Seongjae] vs forever in charge of charisma. Uh. Uh.
[Bae Seongjae] 担当するか一生カリスマ担当するか。あー。あー。
[Bae Seongjae] Aegyo vs charisma.
[Bae Seongjae] 愛嬌かカリスマか。
[Bae Seongjae] One, two, three.
[Bae Seongjae] 1、2、3。
[Stella] Charisma.
[Stella] カリスマ。
[Yuha] Aegyo.
[Yuha] 愛嬌。
[Stella] Oh.
[Stella] おー。
[Yuha] Yes. What about you?
[Yuha] はい。あ、何よ？
[Bae Seongjae] You didn't match.
[Bae Seongjae] 合わなかった。
[Stella] Ah I just
[Stella] あー、私はなんか
[Stella] kind of want to be cool.
[Stella] ちょっとかっこよくなりたいです。
[Stella] Hello.
[Stella] こんにちは。
[Bae Seongjae] The expression you're making while saying that is overflowing with aegyo.
[Bae Seongjae] それをしてる表情があまりにも愛嬌があふれてて。
[Stella] Ah why is Haram aegyo? I think I'm charismatic.
[Stella] あー、ハラムなんで愛嬌？私はカリスマだと思う。
[Yuha] I don't have a charismatic personality, so having aegyo would be
[Yuha] 私はカリスマがある性格じゃないので、その愛嬌がある方がもっと
[Yuha] more comfortable, don't you think? [Bae Seongjae] Ah, I see.
[Yuha] 楽じゃないでしょうか？[Bae Seongjae] あー、そうですか。
[Bae Seongjae] Someone said 'Canada cutie' and yes, someone said their preference is the opposite
[Bae Seongjae] カナダの귀요미だと言ってる方がいて、はい、추구미が何か反対だと言って
[Bae Seongjae] And Yuha, your nickname is 'first love girl'
[Bae Seongjae] そしてユハさんのあだ名は初恋女
[Yuha] Mm
[Yuha] うーん
[Bae Seongjae] Yes, first love visual. Do you personally
[Bae Seongjae] はい、初恋ビジュアル、どう？自分でも
[Bae Seongjae] acknowledge that part too?
[Bae Seongjae] ちょっと認める部分ですか？
[Yuha] Uh, do I acknowledge it? Uh, acknowledging
[Yuha] あー、私が認める？あー、認めるのが
[Stella] I acknowledge it. Right?
[Stella] 認めます。そうでしょ？
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, kind of right? Like a female lead vibe. Someone said 'Architecture Yuha' and yes
[Bae Seongjae] あー、ちょっとそうでしょ？女主人公気質だと。건축학ユハだと言ってる方がいて、はい
[Bae Seongjae] someone said 'where can you find such a pretty first love girl'
[Bae Seongjae] あんなに綺麗な初恋の子がどこにいるんだっておっしゃる方
[Bae Seongjae] Oh Yuha, do you have any nickname
[Bae Seongjae] え、ユハさんは「スっ삐」みたいに、もしかして愛称
[Bae Seongjae] worth sharing like 'Sstobbi'?
[Bae Seongjae] ちょっと公開できるようなのありますか？
[Yuha] For nicknames, I have a nickname called Hamong that my dad gave me
[Yuha] 愛称、私はハモンっていう愛称を父がつけてくれたんですけど
[Bae Seongjae] Hamong, isn't that the delicious thing?
[Bae Seongjae] ハモンってあの美味しいやつじゃないですか？
[Yuha] Woof woof
[Yuha] わんわん
[Yuha] Mm
[Yuha] うーん
[Bae Seongjae] Hamong
[Bae Seongjae] ハモン
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah
[Bae Seongjae] はい
[Yuha] Dad gave it to me, kinda meaning I'm dumb
[Yuha] お父さんがつけてくれたんですけど、ちょっとボーっとしてるっていう
[Stella] Really?
[Stella] 本当に？
[Stella] That's not true, really?
[Stella] 違うでしょ、本当に？
[Bae Seongjae] It's not like spacing out, right?
[Bae Seongjae] ボーっとするじゃないですか
[Yuha] That meaning too, and I space out a lot
[Yuha] そういう意味もあるし、よくボーっともするし
[Yuha] and make some dumb comments to dad
[Yuha] ちょっとボーっとした発言をお父さんに
[Bae Seongjae] No way, to a genius daughter who speaks 3 languages and finds 24 like that, does
[Bae Seongjae] いや、3ヶ国語をしてこうやって24を見つけ出す天才的な娘に、もしかして
[Bae Seongjae] your father perhaps have like three PhD degrees?
[Bae Seongjae] お父様はもしかして博士号を3つぐらいお持ちですか？
[Yuha] No. My dad
[Yuha] いえいえ。うちのお父さん
[Bae Seongjae] Mm
[Bae Seongjae] うん
[Yuha] In front of dad, kinda
[Yuha] そのお父さんの前でちょっと
[Yuha] I don't know. How I was [Bae Seongjae] Like a baby always in front of dad, so dad also
[Yuha] 分からないです。どうだったか [Bae Seongjae] 赤ちゃんみたいにいつもお父さんの前でそうだから、え、お父さんも
[Bae Seongjae] Is he perhaps a T type?
[Bae Seongjae] もしかしてT型ですか？
[Yuha] Yeah ISTJ
[Yuha] はい、ISTJ
[Bae Seongjae] Wow swept competition awards right? Yeah. Plays piano so well, good memory
[Bae Seongjae] わあ、コンクール大賞を総なめでしょ？はい。ピアノもそんなに上手で記憶力も
[Bae Seongjae] and all that. Yeah. Got it.
[Bae Seongjae] 良くて色々と。はい。分かりました。
[Bae Seongjae] Now, next search term. Menu obsession.
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、次の検索語。メニュー固定光。
[Yuha] Mm.
[Yuha] うーん。
[Bae Seongjae] This is Yuha's keyword. They say when you get hooked on one food, you only eat that until you're sick of it.
[Bae Seongjae] ユハさんのキーワードなんですが。一つの食べ物にハマったら飽きるまでその食べ物だけ食べるそうですね。
[Yuha] That's right.
[Yuha] そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh. What food are you hooked on recently?
[Bae Seongjae] え。どんな食べ物に最近ハマってますか？
[Yuha] Right now, just this week I got hooked on honey rice cake.
[Yuha] 今はちょうど今週、ハニー白雪餅にハマってて。
[Bae Seongjae] What's honey rice cake?
[Bae Seongjae] ハニー白雪餅って何ですか？
[Yuha] It's white rice cake with honey inside.
[Yuha] 白雪餅の中にハチミツが入ってるやつなんですけど。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, do they sell that separately these days? Oh,
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そんなの別で売ってるんですか、最近？おお、
[Yuha] I've been eating that every single day for a whole week.
[Yuha] それを一週間ずっと毎日毎日食べてます。
[Bae Seongjae] But if you eat stuff like that, meals might not be appealing, is that separate?
[Bae Seongjae] そんなの食べたら、でも食事はまたちょっと食べたくなくなるかもしれないけど、それは別ですか？
[Yuha] I kinda have meals through snacking
[Yuha] 私はおやつで食事をちょっとする方なので
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, so you're using honey rice cake like meals these days
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ハニー白雪餅でむしろ最近は食事のようにもしてて
[Yuha] Yeah, that's right.
[Yuha] はい、そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, I'll look into honey rice cake. I should try it too. So what other
[Bae Seongjae] や、ハニー白雪餅調べてみます。私も一度食べてみないといけませんね。それじゃあ最近
[Bae Seongjae] foods have you been hooked on recently?
[Bae Seongjae] ハマった食べ物他に何がありますか？
[Yuha] Before honey rice cake, it was mocha bread
[Yuha] ハニー白雪餅の前はモカパン
[Yuha] It was mocha bread, and before that
[Yuha] モカパンでした、その前は
[Yuha] what, yogurt
[Yuha] 何だろう、ヤクルト
[Bae Seongjae] Mm,
[Bae Seongjae] うーん、
[Yuha] Banana Kick. Seaweed soup sujebi, stuff like that
[Yuha] バナナキック、わかめスープのすいとん、そういう感じの
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, your tastes are distinct but also kinda, you know? Yeah.
[Bae Seongjae] あぁ好みがはっきりしてるけど何というか、そうですね
[Bae Seongjae] It doesn't feel like there's a clear pattern - you're really the type who eats something when you're totally hooked on it.
[Bae Seongjae] その流れがあるって感じじゃなくて、本当にハマったらそれを食べるスタイルですね
[Yuha] Yeah. Just that one thing for months
[Yuha] はい、何ヶ月もそれだけ
[Bae Seongjae] Someone said you have grandma taste buds.
[Bae Seongjae] おばあちゃんの好みに似てるって言う方もいますね
[Bae Seongjae] Easy to chew stuff. Yeah. Yogurt and
[Bae Seongjae] 噛みやすい感じですね。ヨーグルトと
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah. And banana snacks. Mm. I see.
[Bae Seongjae] はい、バナナキックと。うん、そうですね
[Bae Seongjae] Oh. Do you also remember good restaurants like that? Like
[Bae Seongjae] あ、じゃあグルメなお店とかも覚えておく方ですか？
[Bae Seongjae] 'I went to this place recently and I really need to come here often.'
[Bae Seongjae] 最近ここ行ってみたらここは本当によく来なきゃって
[Yuha] Yeah. Yeah. With restaurants too, when I get hooked on one, I just keep going there for a really long time
[Yuha] はい、はい。グルメもハマったらそこばかり行って長い間ずっと行く
[Bae Seongjae] What kind of restaurant do you like best?
[Bae Seongjae] 飲食店はどんなお店が一番お好きですか？
[Yuha] What I'm obsessed with lately is seaweed soup sujebi.
[Yuha] 最近ハマってるのがわかめスープのすいとん
[Bae Seongjae] Seaweed soup sujebi. Oh I see. What's the best way to eat that? Do you need to have it with kimchi or something?
[Bae Seongjae] わかめスープのすいとん。あぁそうですね。それって美味しく食べる方法は何ですか？キムチと一緒に食べたりするんですか？
[Yuha] They sell seaweed soup sujebi and water parsley pancake together.
[Yuha] わかめスープのすいとんとセリのジョンを一緒に売ってるんです
[Yuha] Yeah. When you eat them together, it's really delicious.
[Yuha] はい、それを一緒に食べると本当に美味しいです
[Bae Seongjae] Before you leave later, write down where that is for me. I'll go check it out too.
[Bae Seongjae] 後で帰る前にどこなのか書いて帰ってください。私も一度行ってみます
[Bae Seongjae] See, people are saying your taste is exactly like our grandma's. Water parsley, right. Yeah. But like
[Bae Seongjae] ほらね、うちのおばあちゃんと好みが全く同じだって言ってるし。セリですよね。はい。でも何か
[Bae Seongjae] Do you prefer vegetables? More than meat? Or not really?
[Bae Seongjae] ベジタリアンがお好きですか？お肉より？そういうわけではない？
[Yuha] No. I'm actually a really picky eater
[Yuha] いいえ、私はすごく偏食なんですが
[Yuha] I can only eat water parsley pancakes.
[Yuha] セリのジョンだけは食べられます
[Bae Seongjae] And Stella, you're a dessert lover
[Bae Seongjae] そしてStellaさんはデザートラバー
[Bae Seongjae] I see. What kind of desserts do you love so much? [Stella] I like everything
[Bae Seongjae] ですね。どんなデザートがそんなにお好きですか？[Stella] 私はあ、全部好きなん
[Stella] but I really love tiramisu cake and cheesecake.
[Stella] ですけど、私はティラミスケーキとチーズケーキが本当に好きです
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, cake types
[Bae Seongjae] あぁケーキ系で
[Stella] I really love cake
[Stella] ケーキが本当に好きです
[Stella] I love chocolate so much that I eat chocolate every single day
[Stella] チョコレートがすごく好きで毎日毎日チョコレートを食べます
[Bae Seongjae] You eat it every day?
[Bae Seongjae] 毎日食べるんですか？
[Stella] Yeah, almost every day
[Stella] はい、ほぼ毎日
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, so for stuff like tiramisu, do you actually go buy it or order delivery
[Bae Seongjae] おぉじゃあティラミスみたいなのは実際どうやって買いに行ったりデリバリー頼んだり
[Stella] I always order delivery
[Stella] デリバリー頼んでいつもそうです
[Bae Seongjae] Do you share it? Or are you the type to eat it alone?
[Bae Seongjae] シェアして食べます？それとも一人で食べるスタイルですか？
[Yuha] She eats it all herself, and whatever's left over
[Yuha] 全部自分で全部食べて、余ったのはこいつ
[Bae Seongjae] You eat as much as you want and then what's left, how do you want to eat it? [Yuha] She has a really small appetite.
[Bae Seongjae] 食べる分だけ食べて余ったらどうする？[Yuha] 食が細いので
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, she also has a small appetite.
[Bae Seongjae] あぁ、また食が細くて
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, and someone said she's sulking again.
[Bae Seongjae] あぁ、また拗ねるって言う方もいますし
[Yuha] If you do this, she'll be sulking when it's over.
[Yuha] こうなったら終わった後拗ねてる
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, I see. But you're actually in your promotion period right now, and I heard earlier that you had chicken and pizza too.
[Bae Seongjae] あぁそうですね。でも今実際活動期間なのにさっき聞いたらチキンも食べたしピザも食べたって
[Yuha] Yeah. We also had cheesecake today.
[Yuha] はい、今日チーズケーキも食べました
[Bae Seongjae] Cheesecake too - you still eat well while promoting. Still.
[Bae Seongjae] チーズケーキもそれでもよく食べながら活動されてますね
[Yuha] Yeah. We really love eating and we eat well. Yeah. [Bae Seongjae] Then actually
[Yuha] はい、私たちは食べるのがすごく好きでよく食べます。はい。[Bae Seongjae] むしろじゃあ
[Bae Seongjae] during practice period, before promotion period starts, do you manage yourselves more?
[Bae Seongjae] 練習期間、活動期間に入る前にむしろちょっと管理するスタイルですか？
[Yuha] It's always pretty similar, but our thing is let's eat delicious food in moderation.
[Yuha] いつも似たような感じですが、私たちは美味しいものを適度に食べよう
[Stella] That's right. That's right.
[Stella] そうです、そうです
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, so you don't eat until you're stuffed, but you freely choose what you want to eat.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、それでお腹がパンパンになるまで食べたりはしないけど、でもメニューは自由に食べよう
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, that's nice.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、いいですね
[Bae Seongjae] Do you two have compatible food tastes? How is it?
[Bae Seongjae] お二人は食べ物の相性は合う方ですか？どうでしょう
[Yuha] I think we match well. We both like sweet foods.
[Yuha] よく合うと思います。甘い食べ物が好きです。
[Bae Seongjae] Sweet stuff. Oh, then let me check if you really match or not.
[Bae Seongjae] 甘いもの。ええ、それじゃあ合うかどうか一度確認してみましょう。
[Bae Seongjae] This isn't in the script, members.
[Bae Seongjae] メンバーの台本にはありません。
[Stella] Ah, okay.
[Stella] あ、はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Mint choco lovers vs anti-mint choco. One, two, three.
[Bae Seongjae] ミントチョコ派対アンチミントチョコ派。せーの。
[Stella] Anti-mint choco
[Stella] アンチミントチョコ派
[Bae Seongjae] You don't match at all. Right from the start. What about bungeoppang? Red bean vs cream
[Bae Seongjae] 全然合いませんね。最初から。そのたい焼き。あんこたい焼きクリームたい焼き
[Stella] Cream! This one we have to fight over.
[Stella] クリームたい焼き！これはこれは喧嘩しなきゃダメ。
[Bae Seongjae] No need to even do one, two, three. Why why why are you like this again?
[Bae Seongjae] せーのをする必要もないですね。なんでなんでなんでこんなにまた
[Stella] I'm completely red bean and Haram is completely cream, so
[Stella] 私は完全にあんこたい焼きで、ハラムが完全にクリームたい焼きだから
[Stella] I can't understand it.
[Stella] 私は理解できないです。
[Yuha] I don't eat red bean bungeoppang at all either
[Yuha] 私もあんこたい焼きは全然食べないので
[Bae Seongjae] Not at all? [Stella] Not at all.
[Bae Seongjae] 全然食べないんですか？ [Stella] 全然食べません。
[Bae Seongjae] That's not easy, I mean
[Bae Seongjae] それは簡単じゃないですけど、だから何
[Bae Seongjae] Well, bungeoppang usually goes like 1st choice, 2nd choice - you don't completely reject the other side.
[Bae Seongjae] ええ、たい焼きは実は普通1位2位みたいに行くじゃないですか、他方を排斥はしないんですよ。
[Stella] I don't eat cream bungeoppang at all either. I've never even tried it.
[Stella] 私もクリームたい焼きを全然食べません。食べたことがない。
[Bae Seongjae] Never tried it? Haven't even put it to your lips?
[Bae Seongjae] 食べたこと、口にもつけたことないんですか？
[Stella] No.
[Stella] はい。
[Stella] I don't want to eat it.
[Stella] 食べたくないです。
[Bae Seongjae] If you try it once, your mind might change.
[Bae Seongjae] 一度食べてみたらまた気持ちが変わるかもしれませんが。
[Stella] Ah it's fine. No, it's fine.
[Stella] あ大丈夫。いや大丈夫です。
[Bae Seongjae] What about red bean then
[Bae Seongjae] あんこたい焼きをそれじゃあ
[Bae Seongjae] Red bean? [Yuha] Uh, not at all
[Bae Seongjae] あんこたい焼きは？ [Yuha] ええ全然
[Bae Seongjae] Oh I see. For mint choco vs anti-mint choco, who was the mint choco lover?
[Bae Seongjae] ええそうですね。ミントチョコとアンチミントチョコは、はい、誰がミントチョコでしたっけ？
[Yuha] Me, mint choco [Stella] I really hate it.
[Yuha] 私ミントチョコ派 [Stella] 私本当に嫌いです。
[Stella] The worst. The worst of the worst
[Stella] 最悪。その最悪の最悪
[Bae Seongjae] Oh I see. In a way, having compatible food tastes means you don't encroach on each other's
[Bae Seongjae] ええそうですね。ある意味その食べ物の好みが合うっていうのは、お互い侵害を
[Bae Seongjae] territory, so that's why you match?
[Bae Seongjae] しないから合うってことですかね？
[Yuha] Yeah. I guess that's how it works.
[Yuha] はい。そういうことなのかも。
[Bae Seongjae] Then tteokbokki vs chicken. One two three
[Bae Seongjae] それじゃあトッポッキ対チキン。せーの
[Stella] Chicken. [Yuha] Chicken.
[Stella] チキン。 [Yuha] チキン。
[Stella] This is it
[Stella] これだ
[Bae Seongjae] It's not that you hate tteokbokki? [Yuha] I just love chicken too much.
[Bae Seongjae] トッポッキが嫌いなわけじゃなくて？  [Yuha] チキンがすごく好きで。
[Bae Seongjae] What kind of chicken? Fried or seasoned?
[Bae Seongjae] チキンはどんな、フライドですか？それとも味付けですか？
[Stella] Lately I like fried - I used to like seasoned but lately fried
[Stella] 最近私はフライド、もともと味付けだったけど最近フライド
[Bae Seongjae] You used to but oh
[Bae Seongjae] もともとだけどええ
[Yuha] I like seasoned these days
[Yuha]  私は最近味付け
[Bae Seongjae] Seasoned
[Bae Seongjae] 味付け
[Bae Seongjae] Oh
[Bae Seongjae] ええ
[Stella] So now we just order half and half and share peacefully [Bae Seongjae] Oh the food distribution works out well somehow.
[Stella] だから今ちょうど半々で頼んで一緒に平和に [Bae Seongjae] ええ食べ物が何かこう分配がうまくいってますね。
[Bae Seongjae] Do you have a favorite brand? [Yuha] Can I mention the brand?
[Bae Seongjae] もし一番好きなブランドがありましたら？ [Yuha]ブランド言ってもいいですか？
[Bae Seongjae] Chicken brand. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] チキンブランド。はい。
[Yuha] I like Cheogajip Supreme seasoned chicken.
[Yuha] 私はチョガッチプのシュプリム味付け。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah. Ah.
[Bae Seongjae] あ。あ。
[Bae Seongjae] That's really delicious. Yeah. Good choice. Good choice. And
[Bae Seongjae] 本当に美味しいですよねそれ。え。いいですね。いいですね。それと
[Stella] I like BBQ Fried Golden these days
[Stella] 私は最近そのBBQフライドゴールデン
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, so detailed and good.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、細かくていいですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah nice. You both choose well. You're both food connoisseurs.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、いいですね。よく選びますね。お二人とも味の分かる方ですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Someone in the chat says 'Yuha has the same taste as my grandma'.
[Bae Seongjae] チャットでユハはうちのおばあちゃんの好みに合うって言ってますね。
[Bae Seongjae] Alright, sweet potato vs. potato. One, two, three
[Bae Seongjae] では、さつまいもvsじゃがいも。1、2、3
[Stella] Sweet potato - we
[Stella] さつまいも、これは私たち
[Stella] match well on this
[Stella] よく合います
[Bae Seongjae] This is something I kind of knew about. It's not that you hate potatoes?
[Bae Seongjae] ある程度分かっていた部分なんですが。じゃがいもが嫌いというわけではないですよね？
[Stella] I like potatoes.
[Stella] じゃがいも好きです。
[Yuha] I just love sweet potatoes too much
[Yuha] さつまいもがすごく好きで
[Stella] I love sweet potatoes
[Stella] さつまいもを愛してるので
[Bae Seongjae] Then triangle kimbap. Lastly
[Bae Seongjae] それではおにぎりです。最後に
[Bae Seongjae] Jeonju bibim vs. tuna mayo. One, two, three
[Bae Seongjae] 全州ビビンvsツナマヨ。1、2、3
[Stella] Jeonju bibim [Yuha] Tuna mayo
[Stella] 全州ビビン [Yuha] ツナマヨ
[Bae Seongjae] Aha I see. Got it. We looked at triangle kimbap too and
[Bae Seongjae] あはー、そうですね。分かりました。おにぎりまでこうやって調べてみましたが、あ
[Bae Seongjae] looking at it, you two really seem to divide food preferences well.
[Bae Seongjae] 見てると本当にお二人が、あ、食べ物がなんかうまく分かれてるみたいです。
[Bae Seongjae] Now, the next keyword is Han River cycling.
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、次のキーワードは漢江自転車。
[Bae Seongjae] This is Stella's keyword.
[Bae Seongjae] ステラさんのキーワードなんですが。
[Bae Seongjae] You're really good at riding bikes
[Bae Seongjae] 自転車がすごく上手で
[Stella] That's right.
[Stella] そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] You have cycling pride.
[Bae Seongjae] 自転車に自信があるほどだと。
[Stella] Yes. That's right.
[Stella] はい。そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] I saw that Stella told S2U 'If you see me cycling at Han River
[Bae Seongjae] あ、見るとそのステラさんがS2Uに「私が漢江で自転車乗ってる姿見たら
[Bae Seongjae] you'll just fall for me'
[Bae Seongjae] そのまま惚れる
[Bae Seongjae] You wrote something like that
[Bae Seongjae] こう書いたのもあって
[Bae Seongjae] Too cool hehe.
[Bae Seongjae] すごくかっこよくてククク。
[Bae Seongjae] How well do you ride? [Stella] I just fly. When I ride a bike
[Bae Seongjae] どの程度上手なんですか？ [Stella] 私はもう飛んでいきます。自転車乗ったら
[Stella] I just go whoosh like this. I'm just so proud of myself. So
[Stella] そのままシューッとこうやって行きます。もう私すごく誇らしくて。それで
[Stella] Yeah.
[Stella] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Do you ride your own bike? Or do you rent like Ttareungyi?
[Bae Seongjae] そのサイクルに乗るんですか？それともタルンイ借りて乗るんですか？
[Stella] Yeah. I rent
[Stella] はい。借りて
[Bae Seongjae] Ah you fly on Ttareungyi. But Ttareungyi only goes up to 40km at most.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、タルンイに乗って飛んでいくと。タルンイは速度出してもせいぜい最大40kmぐらいしかならないでしょうに。
[Stella] From what I felt, I was flying. That's how it felt.
[Stella] 私が感じた時は飛んでいってると。こう感じます。
[Bae Seongjae] You don't ride hands-free or anything. [Stella] I can do it with one hand.
[Bae Seongjae] 手を離して乗ったりはしないですよね。 [Stella] 片手でできます。
[Bae Seongjae] Just one hand? [Stella] Cool, right?
[Bae Seongjae] 片手だけ？ [Stella] かっこいいでしょ？
[Stella] Or not?
[Stella] 違います？
[Bae Seongjae] Aha, I see. So you don't have your own bike yet?
[Bae Seongjae] あはー、そうですね。それでは私の自転車はまだないんですか？
[Stella] Oh, I have one in Canada but since coming to Korea I can't ride often
[Stella] あ、カナダにあるんですが韓国に来てからはあまりできなくて
[Bae Seongjae] Is the bike in Canada like a really good bike? Or
[Bae Seongjae] カナダにある自転車はなんかすごくいい自転車なんですか？それとも
[Stella] Oh, yeah. I think so.
[Stella] あ、はい。そんな感じです。
[Bae Seongjae] It's not like the one you rode as a kid, right?
[Bae Seongjae] 子供の頃乗ってたやつとかそういうのじゃないですよね？
[Stella] That's right.
[Stella] そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] The one from when you were little, the one dad bought you. Oh
[Bae Seongjae] 子供の頃乗ってたやつ、お父さんが買ってくれたやつ。あ
[Bae Seongjae] Usually in Korea when we talk about cycling pride, it means using expensive equipment
[Bae Seongjae] 普通韓国で自転車に自信があるって言ったら、なんか自転車も少し高価な装備を使うとか
[Stella] Ah so it's not to that extent
[Stella] あ、そこまでは
[Bae Seongjae] Not to that extent, uh, do you ride with all the gear? Or just like that
[Bae Seongjae] そこまでじゃなくて、え、その装備も全部揃えて乗ったりしますか？それともこう
[Bae Seongjae] People who ride bikes, those shoes that clip
[Bae Seongjae] 自転車乗る人たちがその靴に足を
[Stella] into the pedals and stuff like that
[Stella] はめ込んだりとか
[Bae Seongjae] You don't do that?
[Bae Seongjae] そういうのはしないんですか？
[Stella] First time hearing about it.
[Stella] 初めて聞きました。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah I see. In the chat, someone said after listening, it sounds like just regular riding
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そうなんですね。チャット欄に、え、聞いてるとただ私たちが乗るやつ乗るのと
[Bae Seongjae] so they don't know why there'd be any pride in it
[Bae Seongjae] 同じなのになんでプライドがあるのかわからないって言う方がいて
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, someone said they thought you meant unicycling.
[Bae Seongjae] え、私は一輪車乗るのかと思ったって言う方がいて。
[Bae Seongjae] Why are you guys putting our Stella down? Just say it's amazing.
[Bae Seongjae] 私たちのステラをなんで萎縮させるの、ただすごいって言えって。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh but there's an eyewitness account. You rode by noisily near Ttukseom. What's the noisy part?
[Bae Seongjae] え、でも目撃談があります。トゥクソム辺りでにぎやかに自転車に乗って通り過ぎた。にぎやかって何ですか？
[Stella] Uh, music. Ian and I rode together
[Stella] え、今度歌。私とイアンが一緒に乗ったんですけど
[Stella] and we had the music turned up loud
[Stella] 歌を大きめにかけて
[Stella] Ah we had music playing and singing along, singing along
[Stella] あ、歌もかけて歌いながら、歌いながら
[Stella] Uh I remember riding enthusiastically
[Stella] え、一生懸命乗った記憶が
[Bae Seongjae] Uh that sounds so fun
[Bae Seongjae] え、すごくいいですね
[Bae Seongjae] I saw on SNS a few days ago, Dahyeon and Ian on a tandem bike at Ttukseom
[Bae Seongjae] 見るとSNSに数日前にダヒョンとイアンもトゥクソムで2人乗り自転車に乗って
[Bae Seongjae] singing I Got a Boy while zooming by lololol
[Bae Seongjae] I Got a Boy歌いながらさっと通り過ぎるの見たwwwww
[Stella] Yeah
[Stella] はい
[Bae Seongjae] Ah you rode a tandem?
[Bae Seongjae] あ、2人乗りに乗ったんですか？
[Stella] Yeah, I was in the front seat of the tandem and I think I was really good at it
[Stella] そうなんです、私が2人乗りの前の席に乗るんですけど、私が見た時すごく上手いんですよ、あ
[Stella] I think Ian acknowledged it too
[Stella] イアンも認めたみたいな
[Bae Seongjae] Did she acknowledge it from behind? Like 'Stella rides so well'?
[Bae Seongjae] 認めました？後ろで？え、ステラすごく上手だって。
[Stella] 'So good. So good at avoiding things' and stuff like that
[Stella] すごく上手だって。すごく上手に避けたりとか
Uh yeah
え、はい
[Bae Seongjae] Wasn't it hard?
[Bae Seongjae] きつくなかったですか？
[Stella] No.
[Stella] いえ。
[Stella] It was totally easy.
[Stella] 全然楽でした。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, I guess because your lower body is somewhat trained. Oh, nice.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、僕はまたこうある程度下半身鍛えられてるから。おお、いいですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, and also on SNS, someone said two incredibly loud girls on bikes
[Bae Seongjae] え、それとまたSNS反対側からめちゃくちゃ騒がしい女の子2人が自転車で
[Bae Seongjae] were coming down the road and they wondered what it was, but when they could see clearly,
[Bae Seongjae] 道路に来るから何だろうと思ったんですけど、見分けられる距離で見たら、
[Bae Seongjae] Stella was in front and Ian in back.
[Bae Seongjae] 前がステラ後ろがイアンでした。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, they witnessed that rare sight. Someone's asking if you were going around for promotion,
[Bae Seongjae] え、珍しいその姿を目撃しましたね。これ宣伝しに回ったんじゃないかって言って、
[Bae Seongjae] self-promotion. Did the company create viral marketing? [Stella] We kind of had that in mind.
[Bae Seongjae] セルフ宣伝。会社がバイラル回したんじゃないか、これ？ [Stella] ちょっと狙ったのがあります。
[Bae Seongjae] Kind of? Front-Stella-Back-Ian.
[Bae Seongjae] ちょっと？前スト後アン。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, I see. So Dahyeon is Stella's Korean name.
[Bae Seongjae] え、そうなんですね。だからダヒョンさんは今ステラさんの韓国名で。
[Bae Seongjae] Dahyeon and Ian like this
[Bae Seongjae] ダヒョンとイアンがこう
[Bae Seongjae] They saw you both at once it seems. Hmm. So did you just
[Bae Seongjae] 一度に見たみたいですね。うん。それじゃ漢江に行って自転車だけ
[Bae Seongjae] ride bikes at the Han River? Or did you have some ramen too?
[Bae Seongjae] 乗りました？それともラーメンも
[Stella] Uh that time we just rode bikes.
[Stella] え、その時はその時自転車だけ乗ったの。
[Bae Seongjae] Just bikes.
[Bae Seongjae] 自転車だけ。
[Stella] Yeah. We originally planned to eat tteokbokki but riding bikes was so
[Stella] はい。その時元々トッポッキ食べようとしたんですけど、自転車に乗るのがすごく
[Stella] fun that we just rode bikes for like three hours straight
[Stella] 面白くて、3時間ずっと自転車だけ乗って
[Bae Seongjae] Three hours? Uh if it's that much, you can have some pride
[Bae Seongjae] 3時間？え、そのくらいならプライド持つのも分かりますね
[Bae Seongjae] I see. The Han River is really great for biking.
[Bae Seongjae] そうですね。漢江は自転車乗るのにすごくいいですよね。
[Stella] Right.
[Stella] そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] There's lots of Ttareungi bikes too.
[Bae Seongjae] タルンイもたくさんあるし。
[Bae Seongjae] Yuha, did you ever think about joining the biking?
[Bae Seongjae] ユハさんは自転車に参加する気はなかったんですか？
[Yuha] I don't think I'm good at biking.
[Yuha] 自転車があまり上手く乗れないみたいです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, have you never tried? [Yuha] I have tried but
[Bae Seongjae] あ、乗ったことないんですか？ [Yuha] 乗ったことはあるんですけど
[Yuha] I'm not that good at it so it's a bit scary.
[Yuha] そんなに上手な方ではないので、ちょっと怖いです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, are you avoiding it on purpose? In case you get dragged out a few times.
[Bae Seongjae] え、わざと避けてるんじゃないですか？何回も連れ出されそうで。
[Bae Seongjae] In case you keep getting dragged out.
[Bae Seongjae] しょっちゅう連れ出されそうで。
[Yuha] No.
[Yuha] 違います。
[Bae Seongjae] No?
[Bae Seongjae] 違うんですか？
[Bae Seongjae] You use teleportation, so bikes must feel frustrating. Yeah, I see.
[Bae Seongjae] 縮地法を使うのに自転車はちょっとまどろっこしいですよね。はい。そうですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Wow, three hours
[Bae Seongjae] わあ、3時間だったら
[Stella] It really was three hours.
[Stella] 本当に3時間でした。
[Stella] Yeah.
[Stella] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah. Three hours on a tandem bike would be really tough.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。2人用自転車3時間だったら本当にきついですよ。
[Bae Seongjae] I acknowledge that. I acknowledge that. [Stella] Thank you.
[Bae Seongjae] これは認定。認定。 [Stella] ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Okay, the next keyword is tyrant.
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、次のキーワードは暴君。
[Bae Seongjae] This is Yuha's keyword - tyrant.
[Bae Seongjae] ユハさんのキーワードですが、暴君。
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah. So this was a major nickname you were hiding earlier.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。代表的なあだ名を、さっき隠してたのにこれがあったんですね。
[Bae Seongjae] You have this innocent image and that crystal-like voice, but tyrant moments sometimes
[Bae Seongjae] 清純なイメージで何かそのガラス玉のような音色だけど暴君モーメントがたまに
[Bae Seongjae] come out?
[Bae Seongjae] 出るって？
[Bae Seongjae] When do they come out?
[Bae Seongjae] どんな時に出るんですか？
[Stella] Like someone just naturally in situations
[Stella] どんな、え、人がただ自然に、ちょっと
[Stella] you'd never imagine, she just says things in this fun way
[Stella] 想像もできない状況で面白く、こう
[Stella] I think there's something about how she talks. [Bae Seongjae] Suddenly makes shocking statements or something
[Stella] 何かこう話すことがあるみたい。 [Bae Seongjae] 急にちょっとその衝撃発言だとか
[Bae Seongjae] Uh
[Bae Seongjae] え
[Bae Seongjae] Like when asked 'if the members turned into stones'
[Bae Seongjae] そのメンバーたちが石ころに変わったらという
[Bae Seongjae] Yuha would say
[Bae Seongjae] 質問を受けるとユハさんは
[Bae Seongjae] she'd skip stones
[Bae Seongjae] 水切りをするって
[Bae Seongjae] 'Go Stella!'
[Bae Seongjae] さあステラ、行け！
[Bae Seongjae] 'Here we go!' like that lol
[Bae Seongjae] えいちゃ！って言いながらwww
[Bae Seongjae] This is logical in a way too, right? If they're stones, there's no other option.
[Bae Seongjae] これはある意味論理的でもありますよ。そうでしょう？石ころなら方法がないじゃないですか。
[Bae Seongjae] You have to give them the most beautiful ending.
[Bae Seongjae] 一番何か美しい結末を見せてあげなければならない。
[Bae Seongjae] So when asked 'if the members became gum,' she said she'd chew them up.
[Bae Seongjae] それじゃメンバーたちがガムになったらという質問をしたら、くちゃくちゃ噛んじゃうって。
[Stella] Thank you, Yuha.
[Stella] ありがとう。ユハさん。
[Bae Seongjae] In a way, she'd do what best serves their original purpose.
[Bae Seongjae] ある意味そのもともとの目的に最も適うことをしてくれる。
[Bae Seongjae] Logical. Hmm.
[Bae Seongjae] 論理的で。うん。
[Bae Seongjae] Let me try one more. So the members turned into wheels.
[Bae Seongjae] もうちょっとやってみます。それじゃメンバーたちが車輪に変わりました。
[Yuha] Hmm.
[Yuha] うん。
[Bae Seongjae] They turned into wheels.
[Bae Seongjae] 車輪に変わりました。
[Bae Seongjae] What would you do?
[Bae Seongjae] どうしますか？
[Yuha] But then there's no chance they'd turn back into people, right?
[Yuha] でもそれじゃまた人に変わる可能性はないんですよね？
[Bae Seongjae] None. Oh, scary. The look in your eyes while asking is already scary
[Bae Seongjae] ないです。え、怖いな。もう質問してる目つきが怖くて
[Bae Seongjae] No chance, and they can't talk either.
[Bae Seongjae] 可能性なくて、話もできません。
[Bae Seongjae] They're just cockroaches, but I can know who this cockroach is. But they don't know.
[Bae Seongjae] ただの車輪なんですが、この車輪が誰かというのは私は分かるんです。でも彼女は分からない。
[Bae Seongjae] They don't know me either.
[Bae Seongjae] 彼女も私を知らないし。
[Yuha] Then I'd call Cesco.
[Yuha] それなら害虫駆除業者を呼ぶ。
[Bae Seongjae] Without getting my hands dirty
[Bae Seongjae] 私の手を汚さずに
[Yuha] I don't think I could do it.
[Yuha] 私にはできそうにない。
[Bae Seongjae] Without getting blood on my hands. But the members have schedules.
[Bae Seongjae] 私の手に血は付けられない。でもメンバーたちの予定もあるのに。
[Bae Seongjae] So I'd call a professional company to exterminate them all.
[Bae Seongjae] だから専門業者を呼んで完全に駆除する。
[Stella] Thank you.
[Stella] ありがとう。
[Bae Seongjae] What if the members turned out to be aliens?
[Bae Seongjae] それではメンバーたちが実は宇宙人でした。
[Yuha] I'd report them to NASA.
[Yuha] NASAに通報する。
[Bae Seongjae] Kind of outsourcing style. Right? Outsourcing. Yes. NASA, there are aliens
[Bae Seongjae] ちょっとアウトソーシングスタイルですね。そうですよね？外注。はい。NASAここに宇宙人
[Bae Seongjae] here. NASA would take them and experiment on them and stuff
[Bae Seongjae] いますよ。NASAが連れて行って実験したりするかもしれないけど
[Stella] Is that okay? [Yuha] Oh, but aliens are kind of rare
[Stella] 大丈夫？ [Yuha] あ、でも宇宙人ってちょっと貴重な
[Yuha] So they could help the world
[Yuha] そこから世界の役に立つような
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, aliens are good at, uh, persuading and if we research them properly, they might
[Bae Seongjae] あ、宇宙人をうまく、あの、説得してうまくこう、その研究すれば地球に
[Bae Seongjae] help Earth, so it's right for those brilliant people to handle it. Are you sulking?
[Bae Seongjae] 役立つことがあるかもしれないから、本当にその優秀な人たちに任せるのが正しいです。拗ねてるの？
[Stella] No.
[Stella] いいえ。
[Bae Seongjae] Stella seems to be sulking.
[Bae Seongjae] Stellaさん拗ねてるみたいですけど。
[Stella] I'm not.
[Stella] 違います。
[Bae Seongjae] What if the members suddenly disappeared one day?
[Bae Seongjae] それではメンバーたちがある日突然消えました。
[Stella] What should I do?
[Stella] どうしよう？
[Bae Seongjae] They disappeared. They disappeared.
[Bae Seongjae] 消えました。消えましたよ。
[Yuha] But this is just reporting them missing to the police
[Yuha] でもこれはただ警察に失踪届
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, I don't think I can do this anymore. Last one then
[Bae Seongjae] あ、これ以上できそうにないんですが。最後にそれでは、その
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, let me ask Stella this one. The members shrunk to the size of ants.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、これならStellaさんにお聞きしましょう。メンバーたちがアリほど小さくなりました。
[Stella] They're still people but now ant-sized
[Stella] その人なのに今度はアリほどに
[Bae Seongjae] Right. They shrunk to ant size
[Bae Seongjae] そうです。アリほど小さくなって
[Stella] That sounds so fun.
[Stella] すごく楽しそうですね。
[Stella] I'd put them in my pocket and we'd go everywhere together.
[Stella] ポケットに入れて一緒に行きます。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, take them around with you?
[Bae Seongjae] あ、連れて歩く？
[Stella] Oh, that would be so so good. I think so, right?
[Stella] あ、すごくすごく良さそうです。私はそうですよね？
[Bae Seongjae] Put them on a bicycle
[Bae Seongjae] 自転車に乗せて
[Stella] Put them on a bicycle and sing together
[Stella] 自転車に乗せて一緒に歌って
[Bae Seongjae] Should we try riding an 8-person bicycle then?
[Bae Seongjae] じゃあ私たち8人乗り自転車に乗ってみましょうか？
[Bae Seongjae] Yuha, if the members shrunk to ant size
[Bae Seongjae] ユハさんはもしもメンバーたちがアリほど小さくなったら
[Yuha] I'd call Cesco
[Yuha] 害虫駆除業者を呼ぶ
[Stella] They're people though
[Stella] 人間じゃない
[Bae Seongjae] They're people. Just shrunk to ant size. Oh, if they're small you'd just exterminate them all with Cesco?
[Bae Seongjae] 人間ですよ。アリほど小さくなっただけで。あ、小さかったらただみんな害虫駆除で駆除して
[Bae Seongjae] You'd get rid of them.
[Bae Seongjae] しまうんですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Wow.
[Bae Seongjae] わあ。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, I see. Yes. Stella would
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そうですね。はい。Stellaさんはまさに
[Bae Seongjae] Right. Oh, carry them around like keychains. Oh, she would.
[Bae Seongjae] そうですね。あ、キーホルダーみたいに連れて歩いて。あ、そうでしょうね。
[Bae Seongjae] Cesco - totally different outsourcing, Yuha. Mm.
[Bae Seongjae] 害虫駆除、全然違う外注ユハですね。うん。
[Bae Seongjae] Now, there's someone called Prince Suyang Yuha
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、首陽大君ユハという方がいて
[Bae Seongjae] What if the members, then Stella,
[Bae Seongjae] Stellaさん
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] The members have become Tteok-kkochi addicts
[Bae Seongjae] メンバーたちがドバイチューイークッキーになってしまいました
[Stella] Uh, then eat it. You have to eat it. This can't be helped.
[Stella] え、じゃあ食べる。食べなきゃでしょ。これはしょうがないよ。
[Stella] You have to eat that.
[Stella] これは食べなきゃダメだ。
[Stella] Then you have to eat it.
[Stella] じゃあ食べなきゃ。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, since you wait in line to eat it.
[Bae Seongjae] え、並んで食べるものですからね。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, how about you Yuha? [Yuha] Tteok-kkochi varies a lot
[Bae Seongjae] え、ユハさんは？[Yuha] ドバイチューイークッキーはそのお店によって
[Yuha] in taste by store. So comparing the eight different flavors
[Yuha] 味がすごく違うんですよ。だから8つの味を比較してみる
[Yuha] That kind of fun
[Yuha] そんな楽しみを
[Bae Seongjae] There's someone saying it's amazing this team stays together.
[Bae Seongjae] このチームが維持されてるのが不思議だという方もいて。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, tteok-kkochi is hard to resist. But these days, right? Yes. I'll eat it and remember.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ドバイチューイークッキーは我慢できないですよね。でも最近の世の中ではそうでしょ？はい。食べて覚えておきます。
[Bae Seongjae] This feeling. Now, this much makes me understand why she's called
[Bae Seongjae] こんな感じ。さあ、これくらいならなぜ暴君と
[Bae Seongjae] a tyrant. I get it perfectly now.
[Bae Seongjae] 呼ばれたのか分かる気がします。理解できました。
[Bae Seongjae] Now, then the next keyword is shower, which is Stella's
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、それでは次のキーワード シャワーがステラ
[Bae Seongjae] keyword. I heard you shower for a really long time. About how
[Bae Seongjae] さんのキーワードですが。シャワーをすごく長時間されると聞きました。どの
[Bae Seongjae] much time do you spend?
[Bae Seongjae] くらいの時間をかけられますか？
[Stella] Yes, the longest was about 1 hour and 40 minutes I think.
[Stella] はい、一番長かった時が1時間40分ちょっと超えたと思う。
[Bae Seongjae] 1 hour 40 minutes, that's like watching a movie. Did you watch a movie?
[Bae Seongjae] 1時間40分なら映画一本見られますね。映画をご覧になったんですか？
[Stella] Uh I just put on music from my playlist
[Stella] え、ただ音楽を今度プレイリストに流しておいて
[Stella] Sometimes I zone out, sometimes I sing and dance, sometimes I practice
[Stella] ぼーっとする時もあるし、今度歌いながら踊る時もあるし、表情の
[Stella] facial expressions [Bae Seongjae] So you dance in the shower, in the bathroom
[Stella] 演技をする時もあるし[Bae Seongjae] シャワー室で浴室で踊りをして
[Bae Seongjae] and put on performances before coming out. You don't have an indoor bike in there, do you?
[Bae Seongjae] コンサートをして出てこられて、中に室内自転車があるわけじゃないですよね？
[Stella] That would be nice.
[Stella] それならいいですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh
[Bae Seongjae] え
[Stella] Yes
[Stella] はい
[Bae Seongjae] How long does it take for you Yuha? [Yuha] Me, about 20, 30 minutes.
[Bae Seongjae] ユハさんは時間はどれくらいかかりますか？[Yuha] 私は20、30分くらい。
[Bae Seongjae] 20, 30 minutes. Uh, that's just right in a way. Then have the members waiting behind ever complained?
[Bae Seongjae] 20、30分。え、まさに適当な感じですね。それでは後ろにいるメンバーたちがクレームをつけたことはありませんか？
[Stella] I always, ah, it's better now but in the past I would tell everyone to shower
[Stella] 私はいつも、あ、その最近は良くなったけど昔は皆先に
[Stella] first, so they'd shower first and I'd shower last.
[Stella] 洗えって言われて先に洗って、私が一番最後に洗いました。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, but is there a Canadian culture of long showers? I don't really know about that
[Bae Seongjae] え、でもカナダに長く洗う文化があるんですか？それはよく分からなくて
[Stella] I don't think so. [Bae Seongjae] It's just your preference.
[Stella] それは違うと思う。[Bae Seongjae] ただ私の好みだ。
[Bae Seongjae] What's so good about it? Like this
[Bae Seongjae] 何がそんなにいいんですか？こうして
[Stella] Just, you know, like this
[Stella] ただこうして
[Stella] Mm. There's music and I like just staying still like this
[Stella] うん。音楽があってただこうしてじっとしているのも好きで
[Bae Seongjae] In the bathtub like this, just that
[Bae Seongjae] 浴槽でこうまさにその
[Bae Seongjae] Healing?
[Bae Seongjae] ヒーリング？
[Stella] Healing time, and then singing
[Stella] ヒーリングタイム そして歌も歌って
[Bae Seongjae] Singing and dancing too
[Bae Seongjae] 歌も歌って踊りも踊って
[Bae Seongjae] Looking in the mirror
[Bae Seongjae] 鏡を見ながら
[Stella] Uh mirror, just looking at the wall
[Stella] え、鏡じゃなくて壁を見ながら
[Bae Seongjae] Uh looking at the wall, in a way there's that dry ice effect too
[Bae Seongjae] え、壁を見ながら ある意味その自体がドライアイス効果もあって
[Bae Seongjae] with all the steam rising up
[Bae Seongjae] 湯気もざーっと上がっていて、だから
[Bae Seongjae] Uh I see
[Bae Seongjae] え、そうですね
[Bae Seongjae] Have you ever sung I Got a Boy while showering?
[Bae Seongjae] もしかして「I Got a Boy」をシャワーしながら歌ったことある？
[Stella] I have
[Stella] ある
[Stella] Yeah
[Stella] はい
[Bae Seongjae] Right. Dorm shower
[Bae Seongjae] そうですね。宿舎のシャワー
[Bae Seongjae] Are there any set rules? At the dorm?
[Bae Seongjae] 何か決まったルールはありますか？宿舎に？
[Stella] Uh, I don't think so [Yuha] Clean up after yourself and stuff
[Stella] えっと、ないと思います [Yuha] 後片付けちゃんとするとか
[Bae Seongjae] That's about it. Uh,
[Bae Seongjae] その程度。あ、
[Bae Seongjae] So are there any established dorm life rules for Hearts2Hearts members?
[Bae Seongjae] それじゃあ宿舎生活のルールで決まってるのがHearts2Heartsのメンバーたちに
[Stella] We have different dorms so I don't know about here, but at our dorm
[Stella] 私たち宿舎が違うからここは分からないけど、私たちの宿舎は
[Stella] Just clean up after eating and keep your own stuff organized.
[Stella] ただ食べ物ちゃんと片付けて、自分の整理整頓さえすればいい
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, keep it clean.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、きれいに使おう
[Stella] Just keep it clean.
[Stella] きれいに使えばいい
[Bae Seongjae] Common areas. [Yuha] We also just keep it clean.
[Bae Seongjae] 共用スペース。[Yuha] 私たちもきれいに使おう
[Bae Seongjae] Keep it clean. Have there been any problems so far?
[Bae Seongjae] きれいに。今まで何かこんな風に問題が起きたことはないですか？
[Stella] No.
[Stella] はい
[Bae Seongjae] Haven't gotten upset about anything?
[Bae Seongjae] 拗ねたことはないですし？
[Stella] No. None.
[Stella] はい。ないです
[Bae Seongjae] Seems like this question is making you upset
[Bae Seongjae] この質問に拗ねてるみたいな
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. So, H2H's bathroom is Stella's
[Bae Seongjae] はい。さあ、H2Hの浴室はStellaさんの
[Bae Seongjae] solo karaoke room. So is there anything missing at the dorm? Borrowing this opportunity to ask the CEO, we won nine rookie awards, so every time we win an award
[Bae Seongjae] ひとりカラオケ部屋として。それじゃあもしかして宿舎に足りないものありますか？代表さんにこの場を
[Bae Seongjae] we won nine rookie awards, so every time we win an award
[Bae Seongjae] お借りして、私たち新人賞9個取ったんですけど新人賞こうやって賞を一つ取るたびに
[Bae Seongjae] shouldn't we get some new appliances added? Wouldn't that be nice?
[Bae Seongjae] それでも一つずつ何か家電製品も増えたりしたらいいじゃないですか？
[Stella] Mm.
[Stella] うーん
[Stella] I do wish for separate rooms
[Stella] 私は個室が願いではあるけど
[Bae Seongjae] Separate rooms - who's your roommate now?
[Bae Seongjae] 個室、今ルームメイトは誰ですか？
[Stella] Right now I'm sharing with A-NA.
[Stella] 今私はA-NAと一緒に使ってます
[Bae Seongjae] Mm. Isn't it about time you each get your own room?
[Bae Seongjae] うん。個室、それでももうそろそろ部屋一つずつ別々に使う時期じゃないですか？
[Stella] Mm. Yeah.
[Stella] うーん。はい
[Yuha] Separate rooms would be good.
[Yuha] 個室いいね
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Everyone agrees on separate rooms.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。個室には同意
[Yuha] Massage chair? [Bae Seongjae] Massage chair. Ah, just lie down like this and, just once
[Yuha] マッサージチェア？[Bae Seongjae] マッサージチェア。あ、こうやって横になって一回、一回
[Bae Seongjae] satisfyingly uh, release all that stiffness. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] 満足げにあ、こりをほぐせるように。はい
[Bae Seongjae] Good. Again Yuha has that grandma vibe
[Bae Seongjae] いいですね。さすがまたYuhaさんはちょっとおばあちゃん感
[Bae Seongjae] Massage chair.
[Bae Seongjae] マッサージチェア
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. How about an indoor bike?
[Bae Seongjae] はい。室内自転車はどうですか？
[Stella] That would be so good.
[Stella] すごくいいです
[Bae Seongjae] So good?
[Bae Seongjae] すごくいいですか？
[Stella] Please.
[Stella] お願いします
[Yuha] Or beds with electric blankets, heated mattress pads - we need stuff like that.
[Yuha] じゃなければベッドのその電気毛布、温水マットとか必要なんですよ
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, you should have those right away. Right? Good. Yes. Is the TV size okay?
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そういうのはすぐにないとダメでしょ。そうでしょ？いいですね。はい。TVのサイズはどうですか？
[Stella] Really really really big
[Stella] とても完全にとても大きい
[Bae Seongjae] Oh it's big. Uh, good. Yes
[Bae Seongjae] あ、大きいですね。あ、いいですね。はい
[Bae Seongjae] I think these things will happen right away.
[Bae Seongjae] 何かすぐすぐ叶うんじゃないかと思います
[Bae Seongjae] Now, next keyword - rockstar.
[Bae Seongjae] さあ次のキーワード、ロックスター
[Stella] Mm
[Stella] うーん
[Bae Seongjae] They call Stella a rock star.
[Bae Seongjae] ステラさんをロックスターと言います。
[Bae Seongjae] Are you a rock star in the bathroom too?
[Bae Seongjae] お風呂でもロックスターですか？
[Stella] Yeah, I think so.
[Stella] はい、そんな感じです。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, Soda Bottle Baby says Stella's good at singing songs in rock versions.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ソーダボトルベイビーさんが、ステラが歌をロックバージョンで歌うのが上手だって。
[Bae Seongjae] Can any song become a rock version? [Stella] Yes, doesn't matter.
[Bae Seongjae] どんな歌でもロックバージョンになりますか？ [Stella] はい、大丈夫です。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, then Girls' Generation sunbaenims
[Bae Seongjae] あ、じゃあ少女時代の大先輩の
[Stella] I Got a Boy? [Bae Seongjae] Yes, try it in rock style.
[Stella] I Got a Boy？ [Bae Seongjae] はい、一度ロックで。
[Stella] Thank you.
[Stella] ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Someone says it sounds like a rich family's doorbell.
[Bae Seongjae] お金持ちの家の呼び出し音みたいだって言ってますね。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Someone asked to do it again, and someone said it's like Doraemon.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。また叩くの？って言った方もいて、ドラえもんみたいだって。
[Bae Seongjae] Someone just asked if that was Pengsoo.
[Bae Seongjae] さっきペンスーですか？って言った方がいます。
[Bae Seongjae] And can you also play guitar by any chance? If you're a rock star.
[Bae Seongjae] それとギター演奏もできますか？もしかして？ロックスターなら。
[Stella] Uh, of course.
[Stella] あ、当然でしょ。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh.
[Bae Seongjae] あ。
[Stella] Ah, should I try?
[Stella] あ、やってみる？
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Stella] Ah, give me some reaction
[Stella] あ、ちょっと反応して
[Stella] Ah, wait a moment.
[Stella] あ、ちょっと待って。
[Stella] Uh. Yeah. Uh,
[Stella] あ。はい。あ、
[Bae Seongjae] Right. Someone says it's too scary. Sorry, Stella. Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] そうですね。すごく怖いって言った方もいて。ごめん、ステラ。はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, and guitar playing has been revealed, but drum playing
[Bae Seongjae] あ、それとギター演奏は公開されましたが、ドラム演奏はもしかして
[Bae Seongjae] is still unrevealed, I heard. [Stella] That's right.
[Bae Seongjae] まだ未公開だと聞きましたが。 [Stella] そうです。
[Bae Seongjae] Could you possibly show us a bit of drum practice
[Bae Seongjae] もしかしてこの場でドラムをちょっと練習中の
[Bae Seongjae] air drums here?
[Bae Seongjae] エアドラム見せてもらえますか？
[Stella] Air drums, got it. Uh,
[Stella] エアドラム分かりました。あ、
[Stella] Pungchi
[Stella] プンチ
[Stella] Pungdu-pung
[Stella] プンドゥプン
[Stella] I'll stop here. Yeah. Wow
[Stella] ここまでにします。はい。わあ
[Stella] Thank you.
[Stella] ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] The chat says 'Why does that kid do everything?' 'Why does she do everything?' 'Don't overdo it.'
[Bae Seongjae] チャットで、この子なんで全部やるの？なんで全部やってるの？無理しないで。
[Bae Seongjae] Someone calling her Dahyeon-ah
[Bae Seongjae] ダヒョンだって言ってる方がいて
[Bae Seongjae] First of all, when starting, this is prettier.
[Bae Seongjae] とりあえず始める時に、これがこれがもっと可愛いですね。
[Stella] Yeah.
[Stella] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Someone says to put Dahyeon to sleep now
[Bae Seongjae] 誰かダヒョンをもう寝かせろって言ってて
[Bae Seongjae] Someone says 'Dahyeon-ah, learn to say no sometimes.'
[Bae Seongjae] ダヒョン、断ることもしろって言った方がいます。
[Bae Seongjae] Now, Park Seonghyeon says Stella can play guitar, drums, and bass
[Bae Seongjae] さ、パク・ソンヒョンさんが、ステラはギター、ドラム、ベースも扱えて
[Bae Seongjae] and Yuha plays piano well. If all eight Hearts2Hearts members formed a band,
[Bae Seongjae] そしてユハはピアノが上手じゃないですか。Hearts2Hearts8人全員でバンドを
[Bae Seongjae] what instrument would you assign to each?
[Bae Seongjae] 組むとしたら、それぞれどんな楽器を配置しますか？
[Stella] Uh, I'll start with Carmen unnie.
[Stella] あ、とりあえずカルメンお姉ちゃんから。
[Stella] Carmen unnie is
[Stella] カルメンお姉ちゃんは
[Stella] kind of percussion
[Stella] ちょっとパーカッション
[Bae Seongjae] Percussion
[Bae Seongjae] パーカッション
[Stella] Yeah. Kind of
[Stella] はい。ちょっと
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, this pronunciation of 'percussion'
[Bae Seongjae] あ、パーカッション、この発音が
[Stella] Kinda, you know?
[Stella] ちょっと分かる？
[Yuha] What's that?
[Yuha] それ何？
[Stella] That kinda
[Stella] そのちょっと
[Bae Seongjae] Drums?
[Bae Seongjae] 太鼓？
[Stella] Like triangles and stuff like that, various instruments [Yuha] Percussion instruments
[Stella] そのトライアングルもあるしこういうのもあるしちょっと色んな楽器 [Yuha] 打楽器
[Stella] Oh yes
[Stella] お、イエス
[Yuha] Jiwoo unnie always says she wants to play electric guitar.
[Yuha] Jiwooお姉さんはちょっとエレキギターをいつも弾きたいって言うんですよ。
[Yuha] So electric
[Yuha] だからエレキ
[Yuha] And you're piano
[Yuha] そして君はピアノ
[Bae Seongjae] Piano's the winner [Yuha] guitar
[Bae Seongjae] ピアノが当選 [Yuha] ギターがあって
[Stella] JUUN is
[Stella] JUUNは
[Yuha] JUUN should do something cool
[Yuha] JUUNはちょっとかっこいいのやらなきゃいけない気がする
[Stella] Drums and A-NA is
[Stella] ドラムとA-NAは
[Yuha] What's this? Castanets
[Yuha] これ何？カスタネット
[Stella] Castanets
[Stella] カスタネット
[Bae Seongjae] It's surprisingly hard. You gotta keep the beat. Yeah. What about Ian?
[Bae Seongjae] 意外と難しいですよ。リズムに合わせないといけないですからね。はい。Ianさんは？
[Stella] Ian is sogo
[Stella] Ianは小鼓
[Bae Seongjae] Sogo?
[Bae Seongjae] 小鼓？
[Stella] Sogo
[Stella] 小鼓
[Bae Seongjae] The genre's getting really broad.
[Bae Seongjae] ジャンルがすごく広がりますね。
[Stella] Yeah. YE-ON is
[Stella] はい。YE-ONは
[Stella] Vocals?
[Stella] ボーカル？
[Bae Seongjae] Vocals, oh like that, yeah
[Bae Seongjae] ボーカルで、あそういう感じで、はい
[Bae Seongjae] Suddenly sogo? Why does Yuha's taste suddenly
[Bae Seongjae] 急に小鼓？なんで急にユハさんが今度は趣味が急にこう
[Bae Seongjae] jump around sometimes. Like her food preferences too. Oh, fusion-style
[Bae Seongjae] 飛び越える時があるんですよ。その食べ物の趣味もそうだし。あ、フュージョンで
[Bae Seongjae] There's no bass. Bass
[Bae Seongjae] ベースがないですね。ベース
[Stella] Ah
[Stella] あ
[Stella] Bass, I'll do the bass.
[Stella] ベース、ベースは私がやります。
[Bae Seongjae] Both?
[Bae Seongjae] 2つを？
[Stella] Both at the same time [Bae Seongjae] Oh, we might see a crossover group later.
[Stella] 2つ同時に [Bae Seongjae] あ、クロスオーバーグループ後で見れますね。
[Bae Seongjae] Alright. Got it. Let's do K-pop
[Bae Seongjae] さ、そうですね。分かった。K-POPやろうって
[Bae Seongjae] someone said. Yeah. So like this
[Bae Seongjae] おっしゃった方がいます。はい。さ、こうやって
[Bae Seongjae] uh, we had keyword talk time with everyone.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、皆さんと一緒にキーワードトークタイムをやってみましたが
[Bae Seongjae] This time we have that balance game, ah
[Bae Seongjae] 今度はそのバランスゲーム、あ
[Bae Seongjae] time's already up.
[Bae Seongjae] 時間がもう全部終わってしまいました。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah. We sadly have another segment prepared but
[Bae Seongjae] あ。残念ながら用意したコーナーがまたあるんですが
[Bae Seongjae] let's listen to ads and say goodbye to you two.
[Bae Seongjae] CM聞いてお二人とご挨拶しますね。
[Stella] It went by so fast.
[Stella] すごく早く過ぎちゃった。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh really? [Stella] It was fun.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、そうですか？ [Stella] 楽しかった。
[Bae Seongjae] Aw thank you. This is always a comfortable
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ありがとうございます。いつでも私たちの気楽な
[Bae Seongjae] place so come visit anytime.
[Bae Seongjae] 場所ですから遊びに来てください。
[Staff] Did the explanation go
[Staff] 説明はずっと
[Staff] all the way through?
[Staff] できた？
[Staff] Ah
[Staff] あ
[Staff] Should we just skip it?
[Staff] いやしなくてもいいですか？
[Staff] Yeah. The time is
[Staff] はい。時間が
[Staff] Oh, you're not doing it at all? [Staff] Uh no, the time has gone over 40 minutes
[Staff] あ全くしないってことですか？ [Staff] えいや時間は40分を超えちゃって
[Staff] Oh I see, then
[Staff] あそうですかそれじゃあ
[Staff] Uh
[Staff] え
[Staff] We should do closing remarks
[Staff] 終わりの挨拶はしないと
[Bae Seongjae] Let's just do closing remarks and skip the ASMR
[Bae Seongjae] 終わりの挨拶だけするってことでASMRは抜いて
[Staff] When I was explaining earlier, I covered everything else but didn't explain the ASMR part
[Staff] 私がさっきこれ説明する時他のは全部説明してこれ説明してなかった ASMR
[Staff] Then
[Staff] じゃあ
[Staff] Uh so if you want to do it, at the very end
[Staff] えそれでしてくださるなら一番最後に
[Staff] If I ask you to do it at the very end, I don't think we can do that part, so just this would be fine.
[Staff] 一番最後にしてくださいって言ったらこの部分はできそうにないのでこれだけしてくださればいいと思います。
[Stella] Okay. Yeah. With ASMR
[Stella] はい。はい。ASMRで
[Bae Seongjae] Skip the ASMR, just regular
[Bae Seongjae] ASMRは抜いてただただ
[Staff] Just make the sound please.
[Staff] ただ音をしてくださればいいです。
[Stella] Okay.
[Stella] うん。
[Stella] What are you doing after this?
[Stella] 終わったら何してるんですか？
[Bae Seongjae] Huh?
[Bae Seongjae] え？
[Bae Seongjae] Why are you following me after this?
[Bae Seongjae] 終わったらなんでついてくるの？
[Bae Seongjae] Junior, to the rooftop
[Bae Seongjae] 後輩を屋上に
[Bae Seongjae] It feels like you're telling me to follow you
[Bae Seongjae] ついてこいって感じだね
[Stella] Well, yeah
[Stella] まぁはい
[Bae Seongjae] Why?
[Bae Seongjae] なんで？
[Stella] No.
[Stella] いえです。
[Stella] It's not that.
[Stella] 違います。
[Bae Seongjae] I have a live broadcast.
[Bae Seongjae] 生放送があるから。
[Stella] Ah
[Stella] あ
[Yuha] Another radio live broadcast?
[Yuha] ラジオまた生放送？
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah. This is a recording right now. Yes. Live broadcast.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。今は録音で。はい。生放送。
[Bae Seongjae] Yeah. Why, did I do something wrong
[Bae Seongjae] はい。なんで僕が何か間違った間違った
[Stella] No, no.
[Stella] いえいえ。いえいえ。
[Bae Seongjae] Uh, do I need to get scolded?
[Bae Seongjae] え、土下座しないといけないですか？
[Staff] Alright, let's go.
[Staff] さあ、行きます。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Now, Sunday March 1st, Bae Seongjae's TEN today
[Bae Seongjae] はい。さあ、3月1日日曜日ペ・ソンジェのテン今日
[Bae Seongjae] we were with Hearts2Hearts' Yuha and Stella. Ah, time went by
[Bae Seongjae] Hearts2Heartsのユハステラお二人と一緒でした。あー時間が経つのが早すぎて
[Bae Seongjae] so fast, it's such a shame.
[Bae Seongjae] とても残念ですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Just when things were getting fun, like we were about to have some real laughs
[Bae Seongjae] これからちょっと面白くなるそのなんていうか面白いのがバンバン出てきそうなのに
[Bae Seongjae] It's disappointing. We should've had a two-hour broadcast
[Bae Seongjae] 残念です。僕たち2時間放送だったらよかったのに
[Bae Seongjae] Today was so fun for us, I don't know how it was for you two.
[Bae Seongjae] 今日僕たちすごく楽しかったけどお二人はどうだったかわかりませんね。
[Stella] I had so much fun.
[Stella] 私すごく楽しかった。
[Stella] It was so fun. Yeah. Thank you for making us feel comfortable.
[Stella] すごく楽しかったです。はい。楽にしてくださってありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] You must be tired but you came to B-TEN, we're so grateful. Really, to our
[Bae Seongjae] 疲れてるのにまたベテンに来てくださってとてもとてもよかったです。本当に僕たち
[Bae Seongjae] listeners, could you please say goodbye one by one.
[Bae Seongjae] リスナーの皆さんに一度一回ずつ挨拶をお願いします。
[Yuha] Today was so much fun. Next time when we make a comeback, please invite us
[Yuha] 今日すごくすごく楽しかったです。次の次のカムバックの時もまた呼んでくださったら
[Yuha] I'll come anytime. Please listen to RUDE a lot. Thank you.
[Yuha] いつでも来ます。RUDEをたくさんたくさん聞いてください。ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes. Thank you. Yeah.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。ありがとうございます。はい。
[Stella] Yeah. Yeah. I also had so so much fun today and Bae Seongjae was so so good to us
[Stella] はい。はい。私も今日すごくすごく楽しかったし、ペ・ソンジェさんもすごくすごく良くしてくださって
[Stella] so thank you so much. You're the best.
[Stella] すごくすごくありがとうございます。最高です。
[Stella] Please invite us again.
[Stella] また呼んでください。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, this is good.
[Bae Seongjae] おっ、これいいですね。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, good. Yuha, you can't forget that name.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、いいですね。ユハさん、その名前を忘れちゃダメですよ。
[Yuha] Bae Seongjae.
[Yuha] ペ・ソンジェさん。
[Bae Seongjae] Bae Seongjae. Yes. Uh, seems like you got a bit
[Bae Seongjae] ペ・ソンジェ。はい。えっと、ちょっと混乱した
[Bae Seongjae] confused. Well, thank you for coming and next time
[Bae Seongjae] みたいですね。さあ、来てくださってありがとうございます。また次回
[Bae Seongjae] whenever you have time, feel free to come hang out anytime. We're always open.
[Bae Seongjae] お時間があるときはいつでも気軽に遊びに来てください。私たちはいつでも開いてますから。
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Now, we met the two from Hearts2Hearts on Produce 1077. I'll ask you two to do the closing remarks.
[Bae Seongjae] さあ、プロデュース1077でHearts2Heartsのお二人にお会いしました。最後の挨拶はお二人にお願いします。
[Yuha] Yes. This has been Hearts2Hearts' Yuha.
[Yuha] はい。今まで Hearts2Heartsのユハでした。
[Stella] I was Stella. Then we'll turn off the lights.
[Stella] 私はステラでした。それでは消灯します。
[Stella] Dream of Hearts2Hearts. [Yuha] Dream of Hearts2Hearts.
[Stella] Hearts2Heartsを夢見てください。[Yuha] Hearts2Heartsを夢見てください。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah thank you.
[Bae Seongjae] ああ、ありがとうございます。
[Staff] The product introduction
[Staff] 商品紹介を
[Staff] We decided to take turns with Gilly's
[Staff] ギリーさんのと交互に
[Bae Seongjae] Yes?
[Bae Seongjae] はい？
[Staff] In March
[Staff] 3月に
[Stella] Thank you.
[Stella] ありがとうございます。
[Staff] Just one favor please.
[Staff] ひとつだけお願いします。
[Stella] Yes. Yes.
[Stella] はい。はい。
[Stella] That game
[Stella] そのゲームが
[Staff] We decided to get two. Now, can we go straight to this?
[Staff] 二つを取ることにした。さあ、これすぐ行けますか？
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Staff] Just read it once.
[Staff] 一度読んでみてください。
[Staff] Ah, wait. When this red thing comes on.
[Staff] あ、ちょっと待って。これ赤いのが入ったら
[Stella] Ah, yes.
[Stella] あ、はい。
[Yuha] Hello. We're Hearts2Hearts' Yuha and Stella, currently promoting with our new song RUDE.
[Yuha] こんにちは。新曲RUDEで活動中のHearts2Heartsのユハ、ステラです。
[유한] We'll introduce the gifts from Bae Seongjae's TEN. The Han Muncheol dashcam that catches sudden acceleration evidence.
[Yuha] ペ・ソンジェのTENからお贈りするプレゼントをご紹介します。急発進の証拠を掴むハン・ムンチョルのドライブレコーダー。
[Stella] Beat the Day 100 Times is giving away a game-type weight management device, so participate and take the gift
[Stella] 1日を勝ち抜く100番でゲーム型体重管理機をプレゼントしてますので、参加して景品をもらって
[Stella] Sorry.
[Stella] すみません。
[Bae Seongjae] Take it if you want it. Don't if you don't.
[Bae Seongjae] もらうならもらってください。嫌ならやめてください。
[Stella] Yes. Do I need to do it again? Uh
[Stella] はい。もう一度やらないといけませんか？えっと
[Staff] From 'Beat the Day'
[Staff] 1日を勝ち抜くから
[Stella] Beat the Day, Beat the Day 100 Times is giving away a game-type weight
[Stella] 1日を、1日を勝ち抜く100番でゲーム型体重
[Stella] management device, so participate and take the gift.
[Stella] 管理機をプレゼントしてますので、参加して景品をもらってください。
[Yuha] Please also love Hearts2Hearts' song RUDE a lot.
[Yuha] Hearts2Heartsの歌RUDEもたくさん愛してください。
[Bae Seongjae] Thank you.
[Bae Seongjae] ありがとうございます。
[Staff] Thank you.
[Staff] ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Take it or don't, whatever you want.
[Bae Seongjae] もらおうがもらうまいが好きにしてください。
[Bae Seongjae] Thank you. You should be resting but you came here again, so thank you so much
[Bae Seongjae] ありがとうございます。あー、休まないといけないのにこうやってまた来てくださってすごく
[Bae Seongjae] fun. [Yuha] Bye.
[Bae Seongjae] 楽しかったです。[Yuha] バイバイ。
[Stella] Bye.
[Stella] バイバイ。
[Bae Seongjae] Come closer for a greeting. Oh, we need to take a photo first. Hey, photo first.
[Bae Seongjae] 近くで一度挨拶を。あ、写真を先に撮らないと。え、写真を先に撮って。
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Staff] We'll go out this way.
[Staff] ここでこのように出てきます。
[Staff] Act like proper juniors, like proper juniors when taking the photo.
[Staff] ちょっと後輩らしく後輩らしく撮って。
[Writer] Could you two come forward a bit please
[Writer] お二人が前に少し出てきてください。
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Stella] This is our RUDE pose, like this.
[Stella] 私たち、RUDE!ポーズって言ってこうやって。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, okay. Okay.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、オーケー。オーケー。
[Stella] Yes.
[Stella] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Like this.
[Bae Seongjae] こうやって。
[Bae Seongjae] Yes.
[Bae Seongjae] はい。
[Bae Seongjae] Is it okay if I turn like this? [Stella] Right hand up
[Bae Seongjae] なんかこうやって回すのは大丈夫ですか？[Stella] 右手を上に
[Stella] covering the face.
[Stella] 顔を隠して。
[Writer] Hold on.
[Writer] ちょっと待ってください。
[Writer] One, two, three.
[Writer] 1、2、3。
[Writer] One, two, three. Thank you.
[Writer] 1、2、3。ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Ah, thank you.
[Bae Seongjae] あ、ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Oh, the song is so good. [Writer] Please take one selfie
[Bae Seongjae] あー、歌が本当に良いですね。[Writer] セルカ一回だけ撮ってください。
[Stella] Yes. Thank you.
[Stella] はい。ありがとうございます。
[Bae Seongjae] Come close for a greeting once
[Bae Seongjae] ここで一度近くで挨拶を
[Stella] Thank you. It was so fun.
[Stella] ありがとうございます。とても楽しかったです。
[Stella] Bye
[Stella] バイバイ
[Yuha] RUDE
[Yuha] RUDE!
[Stella] Please give us lots of love
[Stella] たくさん愛してね
[Stella] Bye [Bae Seongjae] I learned it. RUDE
[Stella] バイバイ[Bae Seongjae] 覚えた。RUDE!
[Stella] Thank you.
[Stella] ありがとうございます。